[
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 empty boxes, 60 cycles, 58 refrigerator, 1 pigeons, and 11 trees? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            97,
            110,
            18,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 48 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            48,
            66,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 63000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 809000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            77.874,
            868,
            905,
            97
        ],
        "answer": 77.874
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Sunday and returns to the bank 3years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Wednesday",
        "options": [
            "Monday",
            "Sunday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Monday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Flores wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 7cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            6,
            37,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 23 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a man eat?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            23,
            29,
            52,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 16 miles in 3 hours and 19 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.193112280861161,
            5.053413426589385,
            5.791958912158321,
            0.08040201005025126
        ],
        "answer": 0.08040201005025126
    },
    {
        "question": "Rice wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 33cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            16,
            25,
            29,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            19,
            5,
            13,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Angel wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 31cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            9,
            13,
            32,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 14 ohms and 22 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            36,
            14,
            10,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 flower vase, 33 table, 84 cycles, 15 pigeons, and 8 human beings? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            20,
            124,
            66,
            145
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 10 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            3184,
            9131,
            3650,
            10080
        ],
        "answer": 10080
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 56 miles in 4 hours and 22 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.79815082981386,
            1.4675154948136373,
            6.364956790442129,
            20.51908396946565
        ],
        "answer": 20.51908396946565
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            14,
            11,
            25,
            -25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 81. When the sun is at 1 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            24,
            63,
            22,
            106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 8 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            5,
            22,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 56000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 62000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            0.903,
            666,
            527,
            324
        ],
        "answer": 0.903
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 680,
        "options": [
            681,
            680,
            682,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            27,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Ward wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 5.514 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 1.27,
        "options": [
            1.27,
            5.514,
            12.7,
            1.37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vihaan wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 5cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            25,
            40,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 16 miles in 7 hours and 26 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.03587443946188341,
            2.9190519720948216,
            4.666975728859434,
            8.670840030316397
        ],
        "answer": 0.03587443946188341
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Hawkins increased from 583 per month to 939 per month while the salary of Gordon increased from 415 to 702 and of Ferguson increased from 884 to 1000 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Ferguson",
        "options": [
            "Hawkins",
            "Gordon",
            "Ferguson",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            2,
            -27,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 3 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            3577,
            5219,
            3024,
            4781
        ],
        "answer": 3024
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 5 ohms and 20 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            25,
            5,
            10,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 98 miles in 5 hours and 14 minutes?",
        "options": [
            3.2392270377719874,
            9.660237765591216,
            0.31210191082802546,
            1.3296688609191638
        ],
        "answer": 0.31210191082802546
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 14.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            317,
            490,
            49.0,
            396
        ],
        "answer": 49.0
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 16 ohms and 43 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            59,
            688,
            7,
            10,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $20 to the charity and a total of $4468 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            384,
            223,
            708,
            691
        ],
        "answer": 223
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 8 cake , how many cake can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            8,
            10,
            18,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            3,
            1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 18 chocolates , how many chocolates can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            18,
            15,
            33,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 46.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            156,
            97.8,
            125,
            369
        ],
        "answer": 97.8
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 sofa, 83 broom, 23 pair of shoes, 13 snail, and 12 fungi spots? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            36,
            25,
            26,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Castillo wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 25cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            30,
            44,
            37,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wells wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 29cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            37,
            20,
            2,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            4,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 12000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 748000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            968,
            419,
            803,
            0.016
        ],
        "answer": 0.016
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 47. When the sun is at 8 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            21,
            34,
            16,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 79 miles in 9 hours and 41 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.6844445365243725,
            5.703355883217236,
            7.896776397730153,
            13.053356282271945
        ],
        "answer": 13.053356282271945
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 24 tubelight, 86 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 11 crows? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            13,
            133,
            103,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            5,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            6,
            22,
            7,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 bed, 33 cycles, 47 table, 12 snail, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            231,
            0,
            143,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 11 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            11,
            22,
            33,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 37 ohms and 38 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            1406,
            38,
            75,
            37,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            5,
            -16,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 27 miles in 6 hours and 38 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.580191883935615,
            0.0678391959798995,
            7.692950204103343,
            1.5019596109529574
        ],
        "answer": 0.0678391959798995
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 24 tubelight, 86 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 11 crows? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 80,
        "options": [
            0,
            211,
            208,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 17 lemons , how many lemons can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            17,
            28,
            45,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 tubelight, 25 broom, 92 flower vase, 3 crows, and 2 fungi spots? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            95,
            6,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 table, 58 empty boxes, 12 flower vase, 5 fungi spots, and 1 trees? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            71,
            84,
            17,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 8 cake , how many cake can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            8,
            9,
            17,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 50 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            28,
            94,
            8,
            50,
            2200
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 chair, 26 pair of shoes, 88 cycles, 15 cockroaches, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            60,
            10,
            78,
            106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 table, 58 empty boxes, 12 flower vase, 5 fungi spots, and 1 trees? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            -1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 33cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            5,
            38,
            22,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mohammed wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 15cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            3,
            18,
            14,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            -1,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 14 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            4,
            -11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 18 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            24,
            12,
            -24
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            8,
            5,
            6,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 8 years old in the year 1179.In his greatest win, he looted 263183508 of 6514570141 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1277,
            1406,
            1600,
            1171
        ],
        "answer": 1171
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Gordon increased from 676 per month to 815 per month while the salary of Grant increased from 905 to 954 and of Bennett increased from 814 to 867 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Bennett",
        "options": [
            "Gordon",
            "Grant",
            "Bennett",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $22 to the charity and a total of $9824 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            671,
            869,
            949,
            446
        ],
        "answer": 446
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 empty boxes, 73 flower vase, 53 mat, 10 fungi spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            22,
            78,
            23,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $86 to the charity and a total of $5028 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            626,
            574,
            58,
            577
        ],
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 chair, 7 tubelight, 2 bed, 9 algae spots, and 12 dog? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            22,
            21,
            11,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            5,
            3,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 6 ohms and 32 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            6,
            38,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 41 ohms and 21 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            62,
            41,
            21,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Washington wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 7.764 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 6.41,
        "options": [
            6.41,
            64.1,
            7.764,
            6.51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 chair, 39 couch, 5 bed, 13 people, and 11 algae spots? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            18,
            50,
            24,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aditya wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 36cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            9,
            37,
            37,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 36 ohms and 28 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            64,
            4,
            1008,
            0,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 88 pair of shoes, 94 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 5 plants? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            118,
            184,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            4,
            11,
            5,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 9 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            9,
            12,
            21,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Miller wants to put a car in a road.The road is 8.892 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 2.39,
        "options": [
            23.900000000000002,
            2.39,
            8.892,
            2.49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Watson began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 140,
        "options": [
            0,
            141,
            142,
            140
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 88 pair of shoes, 94 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 5 plants? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            190,
            188,
            189
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            5,
            -26,
            21,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 cycles, 77 empty boxes, 12 bed, 4 human beings, and 11 cat? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            58,
            292,
            375,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 11 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            2,
            11,
            12,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 48 ohms and 48 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            96,
            48,
            48,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 19000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 149000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            580,
            716,
            127516.779,
            209
        ],
        "answer": 127516.779
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            7,
            0,
            5,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Phillips wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 9.853 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 2.57,
        "options": [
            2.67,
            2.57,
            25.7,
            9.853
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            8,
            5,
            5,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            30,
            13,
            17,
            -30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 18 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            24,
            12,
            -24
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 36 ohms and 28 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            36,
            28,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anika wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 9.766 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 1.68,
        "options": [
            1.68,
            1.78,
            16.8,
            9.766
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 40 ohms and 31 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 25 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            55,
            31,
            1240,
            25,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            7,
            3,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Morales wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 33cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            30,
            20,
            36,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 fan, 33 empty boxes, 30 tubelight, 2 dog, and 12 cat? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            0,
            68,
            216,
            400
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $52 to the charity and a total of $14802 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            669,
            284,
            313,
            494
        ],
        "answer": 284
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            8,
            9,
            10,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 24 ohms and 25 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            8,
            600,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kelly began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 200,
        "options": [
            0,
            202,
            200,
            201
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            10,
            4,
            3,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 chair, 96 pair of shoes, 13 bed, 1 crows, and 5 human beings? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            7,
            6,
            14,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 20 lemons , how many lemons can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            20,
            28,
            48,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 41.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            300,
            498,
            129.1,
            304
        ],
        "answer": 129.1
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 8 cake , how many cake can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            8,
            7,
            15,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            3,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            8,
            26,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            22,
            3,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 table, 58 empty boxes, 12 flower vase, 5 fungi spots, and 1 trees? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            59,
            86,
            89,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            8,
            3,
            4,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 27 watermelon , how many watermelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            27,
            21,
            48,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            0,
            11,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            5,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 9 sofa, 93 couch, 11 people, and 7 cockroaches? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 104,
        "options": [
            11,
            105,
            104,
            104
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ortiz wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 37cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            45,
            15,
            21,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            5,
            -25,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 88. When the sun is at 77 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            96,
            22,
            88,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jordan began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 208,
        "options": [
            210,
            208,
            209,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 13 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            28,
            25,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 7 years old in the year 1156.In his greatest win, he looted 338535455 of 8088160096 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1149,
            1487,
            1552,
            1817
        ],
        "answer": 1149
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 8 feet by 2 feet?",
        "options": [
            2304,
            3800,
            5515,
            1766
        ],
        "answer": 2304
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 28 watermelon , how many watermelon can a man eat?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            28,
            12,
            40,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            5,
            14,
            0,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 26 miles in 3 hours and 30 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.265701559134984,
            9.308368534391485,
            0.12380952380952381,
            5.312699776141056
        ],
        "answer": 0.12380952380952381
    },
    {
        "question": "Aadhya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 680,
        "options": [
            681,
            682,
            0,
            680
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 73 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 5/6 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            30,
            27,
            60.83,
            38
        ],
        "answer": 60.83
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 8 men, 8 women, 9 children of less than 10 years, 9 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            104,
            34,
            0,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 25 apples , how many apples can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            25,
            26,
            51,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 8 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            1,
            20,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 27 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            9,
            20,
            54,
            729,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $82 to the charity and a total of $5436 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            66,
            324,
            97,
            351
        ],
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarav wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 12cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            4,
            14,
            8,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 37 tubelight, 38 cycles, 12 crows, and 10 snail? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            47,
            50,
            86,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            3,
            -1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 broom, 20 pair of shoes, 43 sofa, 11 cat, and 13 crows? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            33,
            77,
            76,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            4,
            10,
            1,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -28,
            28,
            22,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Boyd increased from 365 per month to 815 per month while the salary of Mcdonald increased from 655 to 944 and of Jenkins increased from 833 to 909 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Jenkins",
        "options": [
            "Boyd",
            "Mcdonald",
            "Jenkins",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Snyder wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 4.743 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 1.63,
        "options": [
            4.743,
            1.63,
            16.299999999999997,
            1.73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sara wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 33cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            5,
            19,
            36,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 83 grapes , how many grapes can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 196,
        "options": [
            83,
            196,
            279,
            113
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 5years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Wednesday",
        "options": [
            "Thursday",
            "Wednesday",
            "tuesday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            20,
            -23,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            7,
            4,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 flower vase, 43 sofa, 86 mat, 9 fungi spots, and 3 dog? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 130,
        "options": [
            95,
            131,
            44,
            130
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Simmons wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 7.293 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 2.96,
        "options": [
            7.293,
            29.6,
            3.06,
            2.96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stephens wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 38cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            19,
            40,
            16,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 13 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            28,
            25,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Ross began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 560,
        "options": [
            562,
            560,
            561,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Patterson wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 32cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            33,
            12,
            15,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 21 ohms and 46 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            46,
            9,
            21,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Advaith wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 6cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            2,
            7,
            34,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 30 ohms and 10 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            40,
            30,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 2 men, 5 women, 7 children of less than 10 years, 2 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            109,
            16,
            0,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            8,
            2,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 refrigerator, 5 bed, 45 couch, 8 pigeons, and 7 dog? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            0,
            17,
            124,
            242
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 69 broom, 92 mat, 1 cockroaches, and 8 cat? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            168,
            167,
            169,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Williams earns $19 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $2 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Williams was paid $1501, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            32,
            381,
            79,
            383
        ],
        "answer": 79
    },
    {
        "question": "Foster wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 7.606 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 5.12,
        "options": [
            5.22,
            5.12,
            7.606,
            51.2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 37 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            55,
            18,
            37,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 95000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 926000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            659,
            102.592,
            479,
            264
        ],
        "answer": 102.592
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 4.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            185,
            17.2,
            486,
            482
        ],
        "answer": 17.2
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 11 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            11,
            28,
            39,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 7 feet by 5 feet?",
        "options": [
            9981,
            5040,
            4741,
            5875
        ],
        "answer": 5040
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 37 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            55,
            666,
            12,
            0,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 33 ohms and 9 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            9,
            33,
            10,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            8,
            17,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 sofa, 84 couch, 55 pair of shoes, 11 fungi spots, and 12 human beings? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            66,
            91,
            23,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 61000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 157000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            725,
            481,
            0.389,
            935
        ],
        "answer": 0.389
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            7,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Jimenez wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 3.644 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 1.62,
        "options": [
            1.62,
            1.7200000000000002,
            3.644,
            16.200000000000003
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 43 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            0,
            1161,
            10,
            70,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 59 grapes , how many grapes can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            59,
            72,
            131,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Russell wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 27cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            20,
            25,
            24,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Pari wants to put a house in a street.The street is 9.95 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 1.92,
        "options": [
            19.2,
            2.02,
            9.95,
            1.92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 31. When the sun is at 89 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            97,
            94,
            9,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 refrigerator, 5 bed, 45 couch, 8 pigeons, and 7 dog? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            48,
            79,
            77,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 35 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            79,
            10,
            35,
            1540,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 12 ohms and 9 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 15 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            45,
            108,
            21,
            15,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 sofa, 83 broom, 23 pair of shoes, 13 snail, and 12 fungi spots? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 115,
        "options": [
            36,
            116,
            115,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Russell wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 16cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            5,
            35,
            45,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Olson wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 25cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            2,
            17,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -28,
            28,
            22,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Anya earns $7 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $4 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Anya was paid $1487, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            171,
            185,
            188,
            28
        ],
        "answer": 171
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 tubelight, 89 empty boxes, 24 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 7 plants? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            136,
            181,
            0,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Payne wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 40cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            4,
            45,
            29,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Chavez wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 29cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            8,
            41,
            13,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jones wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 8cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            18,
            32,
            33,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 sofa, 84 couch, 55 pair of shoes, 11 fungi spots, and 12 human beings? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            147,
            114,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 85 grapes , how many grapes can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 142,
        "options": [
            85,
            142,
            227,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 bed, 43 broom, 43 refrigerator, 10 algae spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            99,
            114,
            100,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 24 chocolates , how many chocolates can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            24,
            28,
            52,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 50 ohms and 20 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            50,
            20,
            7,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 17 ohms and 7 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            4,
            12,
            0,
            119,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aaradhya wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 4.931 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 3.75,
        "options": [
            3.75,
            3.85,
            4.931,
            37.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 24 tubelight, 86 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 11 crows? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            129,
            117,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 88 grapes , how many grapes can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            88,
            96,
            184,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            27,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 26 ohms and 15 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            26,
            41,
            5,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tran began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 616,
        "options": [
            0,
            617,
            618,
            616
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -24,
            24,
            4,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "Sullivan wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 13cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            36,
            21,
            35,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 flower vase, 90 pair of shoes, 18 refrigerator, 3 cockroaches, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            0,
            215,
            167,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 31cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            39,
            21,
            9,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            0,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 80000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 748000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            0.107,
            315,
            794,
            836
        ],
        "answer": 0.107
    },
    {
        "question": "Aditya wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 22cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            3,
            8,
            27,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            5,
            6,
            1,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Akshara wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 23cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            15,
            8,
            29,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 9 watermelon , how many watermelon can a man eat?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            9,
            15,
            24,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            8,
            3,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 25 chair, 99 fan, 3 snail, and 5 trees? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 125,
        "options": [
            126,
            102,
            26,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $70 to the charity and a total of $4718 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            254,
            748,
            67,
            28
        ],
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "Foster began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 450,
        "options": [
            452,
            0,
            451,
            450
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            5,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 59 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/10 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            11,
            17.7,
            44,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 17.7
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $70 to the charity and a total of $8400 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            845,
            328,
            120,
            735
        ],
        "answer": 120
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 7 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            5186,
            7056,
            1026,
            2603
        ],
        "answer": 7056
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 64 miles in 6 hours and 22 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.8762554679201986,
            10.052356020942408,
            9.063751636687167,
            1.1952875094576352
        ],
        "answer": 10.052356020942408
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 mat, 40 couch, 77 cycles, 4 plants, and 14 cat? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            104,
            111,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            4,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            9,
            14,
            6,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 20 miles in 3 hours and 9 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.4936599279063756,
            8.522575889333375,
            9.871684013576722,
            6.349206349206349
        ],
        "answer": 6.349206349206349
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 50 ohms and 20 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            17,
            20,
            70,
            7,
            1000
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 9 ohms and 12 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            0,
            10,
            108,
            21,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Diaz wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 8cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            28,
            28,
            25,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1591.In his greatest win, he looted 820338205 of 1989471532 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1726,
            1846,
            1576,
            1762
        ],
        "answer": 1576
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 76. When the sun is at 170 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            55,
            48,
            86,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Ramirez increased from 510 per month to 625 per month while the salary of Gray increased from 551 to 746 and of Gomez increased from 504 to 811 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Gomez",
        "options": [
            "Ramirez",
            "Gray",
            "Gomez",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 50 ohms and 47 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            97,
            47,
            50,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 refrigerator, 22 fan, 97 cycles, 3 algae spots, and 13 snail? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 116,
        "options": [
            116,
            134,
            138,
            128
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 mat, 63 chair, 28 fan, 12 trees, and 1 cat? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            110,
            69,
            110,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 57. When the sun is at 61 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            98,
            15,
            94,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 table, 7 refrigerator, 53 bed, 2 human beings, and 15 snail? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            72,
            18,
            71,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 29 sofa, 61 tubelight, 4 snail, and 12 dog? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            17,
            16,
            65,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            3,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Barnes wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 21cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            18,
            23,
            6,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            19,
            7,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 flower vase, 90 pair of shoes, 18 refrigerator, 3 cockroaches, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            100,
            21,
            118,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            5,
            -26,
            21,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 85 miles in 7 hours and 43 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.512173831824227,
            3.631935528976144,
            4.047244831911281,
            11.01511879049676
        ],
        "answer": 11.01511879049676
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            1,
            8,
            15,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 6 feet by 4 feet?",
        "options": [
            3456,
            3805,
            2032,
            4770
        ],
        "answer": 3456
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            1,
            6,
            5,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 21 lemons , how many lemons can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            21,
            23,
            44,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 7 years old in the year 1868.In his greatest win, he looted 76495090 of 715549757 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1868,
            1881,
            1876,
            1861
        ],
        "answer": 1861
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 broom, 20 pair of shoes, 43 sofa, 11 cat, and 13 crows? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            65,
            21,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $92 to the charity and a total of $6582 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            64,
            71,
            879,
            241
        ],
        "answer": 71
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 76 grapes , how many grapes can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 198,
        "options": [
            76,
            198,
            274,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 bed, 57 table, 12 fan, 13 fungi spots, and 9 people? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            66,
            23,
            22,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 13 apples , how many apples can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            13,
            8,
            21,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 5 feet by 1 feet?",
        "options": [
            4424,
            9705,
            720,
            6554
        ],
        "answer": 720
    },
    {
        "question": "Mitchell wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 33cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            16,
            8,
            35,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 25 chocolates , how many chocolates can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            25,
            17,
            42,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 62 miles in 10 hours and 12 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.862005775224362,
            9.725490196078432,
            9.585728804083814,
            3.74302192844132
        ],
        "answer": 9.725490196078432
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            1,
            10,
            5,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $74 to the charity and a total of $8292 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            418,
            112,
            912,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "question": "Wallace wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 24cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            38,
            14,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 21 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            6,
            11,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 chair, 96 pair of shoes, 13 bed, 1 crows, and 5 human beings? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            73,
            60,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 7 ohms and 29 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            36,
            0,
            203,
            3,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 21000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 911000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            651,
            0.023,
            145,
            920
        ],
        "answer": 0.023
    },
    {
        "question": "Diya wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 31cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            10,
            35,
            16,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            25,
            -25,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            0,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Diya wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 6.209 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 3.48,
        "options": [
            3.58,
            3.48,
            6.209,
            34.8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            27,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 29 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 17 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            47,
            17,
            18,
            38,
            522
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Burns began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 582,
        "options": [
            0,
            583,
            584,
            582
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 5000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 542000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            734,
            198,
            9.225,
            392
        ],
        "answer": 9.225
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 34.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            480,
            275.4,
            373,
            429
        ],
        "answer": 275.4
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 93000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 208000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            975,
            447.115,
            326,
            31
        ],
        "answer": 447.115
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 40 cycles, 8 fan, 7 human beings, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            49,
            58,
            15,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 35 ohms and 30 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            65,
            3,
            30,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            27,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 70 miles in 4 hours and 33 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.890255635470623,
            0.41025641025641024,
            5.366647659029148,
            9.461959440374411
        ],
        "answer": 0.41025641025641024
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            5,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James wants to put a car in a road.The road is 5.787 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 2.36,
        "options": [
            2.36,
            5.787,
            2.46,
            23.599999999999998
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 20.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            80.6,
            485,
            219,
            132
        ],
        "answer": 80.6
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 46.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            283.0,
            305,
            486,
            372
        ],
        "answer": 283.0
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 empty boxes, 60 cycles, 58 refrigerator, 1 pigeons, and 11 trees? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            59,
            13,
            12,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 86 grapes , how many grapes can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 159,
        "options": [
            86,
            159,
            245,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            19,
            7,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "Cooper wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 29cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            23,
            33,
            43,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 100 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 2/6 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            91,
            32,
            12,
            33.33
        ],
        "answer": 33.33
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 54. When the sun is at 171 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 82,
        "options": [
            5,
            17,
            9,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 27 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            27,
            25,
            52,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            9,
            1,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 65000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 296000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            219.595,
            956,
            497,
            773
        ],
        "answer": 219.595
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            10,
            4,
            5,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Darsh began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            32,
            34,
            33,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 11.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            402,
            270,
            33.3,
            256
        ],
        "answer": 33.3
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            9,
            0,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 50 fan, 58 sofa, 4 cat, and 3 dog? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            39,
            11,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 empty boxes, 83 flower vase, 50 broom, 7 trees, and 9 dog? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 148,
        "options": [
            57,
            148,
            149,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 31 miles in 1 hours and 12 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.032486461523079,
            41.333333333333336,
            3.085871828781383,
            6.431251334814355
        ],
        "answer": 41.333333333333336
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 41.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            391,
            414,
            288.5,
            480
        ],
        "answer": 288.5
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarav earns $16 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $4 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Aarav was paid $4920, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            282,
            266,
            261,
            279
        ],
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 14.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            186,
            35.8,
            250,
            173
        ],
        "answer": 35.8
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            4,
            9,
            10,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            7,
            12,
            6,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 10 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            5654,
            8053,
            7735,
            10080
        ],
        "answer": 10080
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 18 lemons , how many lemons can a man eat?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            18,
            29,
            47,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 19 watermelon , how many watermelon can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            19,
            25,
            44,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            18,
            4,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Porter wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 6cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            21,
            12,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            10,
            1,
            18,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 6 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            6048,
            2795,
            8832,
            5901
        ],
        "answer": 6048
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 12 bed, 39 cycles, 13 crows, and 6 cat? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            19,
            19,
            20,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 25 lemons , how many lemons can a man eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            25,
            16,
            41,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            5,
            -25,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 30 ohms and 10 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            12,
            40,
            8,
            300,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 37 tubelight, 38 cycles, 12 crows, and 10 snail? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            87,
            88,
            36,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 19 ohms and 32 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            5,
            2,
            0,
            608,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Moreno began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 820,
        "options": [
            0,
            821,
            822,
            820
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -19,
            18,
            19,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 7. When the sun is at 60 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            104,
            5,
            108,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 25 chair, 99 fan, 3 snail, and 5 trees? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            26,
            9,
            102,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anaya wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 4.614 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 2.84,
        "options": [
            2.94,
            4.614,
            28.4,
            2.84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fox wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 25cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            37,
            24,
            13,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 tubelight, 25 broom, 92 flower vase, 3 crows, and 2 fungi spots? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            11,
            124,
            64,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 16 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            22,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            10,
            0,
            4,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 94. When the sun is at 15 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            41,
            39,
            106,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Johnson wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 5.441 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 3.69,
        "options": [
            5.441,
            36.9,
            3.79,
            3.69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 69 broom, 92 mat, 1 cockroaches, and 8 cat? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            217,
            229,
            0,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 broom, 23 fan, 5 couch, 10 algae spots, and 5 trees? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            19,
            51,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            30,
            13,
            17,
            -30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 40 cycles, 8 fan, 7 human beings, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            68,
            66,
            17,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 5 men, 7 women, 4 children of less than 10 years, 5 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            107,
            21,
            0,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tran wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 25cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            15,
            9,
            31,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hughes began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 102,
        "options": [
            104,
            0,
            103,
            102
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Olson wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 6.256 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 3.83,
        "options": [
            3.93,
            3.83,
            6.256,
            38.3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Perez wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 5cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            20,
            12,
            4,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 chair, 7 tubelight, 2 bed, 9 algae spots, and 12 dog? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            23,
            31,
            14,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 80. When the sun is at 19 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 80,
        "options": [
            80,
            63,
            23,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 empty boxes, 83 flower vase, 50 broom, 7 trees, and 9 dog? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            20,
            332,
            248,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 mat, 63 chair, 28 fan, 12 trees, and 1 cat? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            71,
            14,
            40,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Davis increased from 929 per month to 951 per month while the salary of Ruiz increased from 908 to 909 and of Cunningham increased from 567 to 988 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Cunningham",
        "options": [
            "Davis",
            "Ruiz",
            "Cunningham",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 29.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            473,
            302,
            292,
            122.2
        ],
        "answer": 122.2
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 broom, 33 refrigerator, 41 pair of shoes, 8 cat, and 11 human beings? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            20,
            49,
            19,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            10,
            -25,
            15,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 12 ohms and 9 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            12,
            21,
            0,
            4,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 18.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            77.6,
            402,
            351,
            272
        ],
        "answer": 77.6
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 8 chocolates , how many chocolates can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            8,
            9,
            17,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 chair, 96 pair of shoes, 13 bed, 1 crows, and 5 human beings? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            72,
            105,
            6,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 chair, 26 pair of shoes, 88 cycles, 15 cockroaches, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            103,
            32,
            121,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 1000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 905000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            595,
            99,
            0.001,
            201
        ],
        "answer": 0.001
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 92 miles in 8 hours and 31 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.1891893065092765,
            8.873073614053482,
            9.894949512948266,
            0.18003913894324852
        ],
        "answer": 0.18003913894324852
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 refrigerator, 22 fan, 97 cycles, 3 algae spots, and 13 snail? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 125,
        "options": [
            0,
            152,
            125,
            198
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 6 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            7164,
            6048,
            2328,
            8150
        ],
        "answer": 6048
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 12 ohms and 9 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            12,
            9,
            7,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            -27,
            22,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            2,
            -27,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            1,
            7,
            21,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 pair of shoes, 19 bed, 60 tubelight, 5 cockroaches, and 15 cat? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            307,
            0,
            177,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gardner wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 20cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            12,
            34,
            37,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 8 lemons , how many lemons can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            8,
            27,
            35,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 95 miles in 6 hours and 4 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.260989010989011,
            4.132384616167043,
            8.44442622829051,
            9.866438607392986
        ],
        "answer": 0.260989010989011
    },
    {
        "question": "Ahana began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            36,
            0,
            37,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            5,
            -26,
            21,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            5,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 bed, 33 cycles, 47 table, 12 snail, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            38,
            33,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            1,
            3,
            2,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 6 feet by 8 feet?",
        "options": [
            6092,
            3223,
            6912,
            5717
        ],
        "answer": 6912
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 cycles, 75 bed, 7 sofa, 2 snail, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            26,
            5,
            39,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 empty boxes, 73 flower vase, 53 mat, 10 fungi spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            19,
            140,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 tubelight, 89 empty boxes, 24 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 7 plants? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 125,
        "options": [
            26,
            126,
            101,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 5 men, 7 women, 3 children of less than 10 years, 8 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            105,
            23,
            0,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 100. When the sun is at 26 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 101,
        "options": [
            101,
            70,
            20,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 6 feet by 10 feet?",
        "options": [
            7491,
            880,
            7379,
            8640
        ],
        "answer": 8640
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $70 to the charity and a total of $17544 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            834,
            94,
            250,
            398
        ],
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 18 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            24,
            12,
            -24
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            5,
            -25,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 28 chocolates , how many chocolates can a man eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            28,
            24,
            52,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mason wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 3.973 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 1.97,
        "options": [
            19.7,
            1.97,
            3.973,
            2.07
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bennett wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 25cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            18,
            13,
            21,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wright wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 7.096 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 6.0,
        "options": [
            6.0,
            6.1,
            7.096,
            60.0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 12 ohms and 9 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            21,
            9,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 bed, 43 broom, 43 refrigerator, 10 algae spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 97,
        "options": [
            53,
            97,
            98,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 12 bed, 39 cycles, 13 crows, and 6 cat? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            58,
            59,
            19,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $50 to the charity and a total of $14360 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            990,
            898,
            287,
            118
        ],
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 chair, 7 tubelight, 2 bed, 9 algae spots, and 12 dog? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            133,
            0,
            19,
            188
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ellis wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 8.618 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 2.11,
        "options": [
            2.11,
            21.099999999999998,
            8.618,
            2.21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 38.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            171,
            354,
            119.1,
            141
        ],
        "answer": 119.1
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            14,
            1,
            8,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 180 grapes , how many grapes can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            180,
            84,
            264,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 refrigerator, 5 bed, 45 couch, 8 pigeons, and 7 dog? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            20,
            53,
            16,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 42.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            394,
            378.8,
            484,
            444
        ],
        "answer": 378.8
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 27. When the sun is at 155 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            6,
            19,
            55,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 30 flower vase, 24 sofa, 2 plants, and 2 dog? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            54,
            32,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 39 miles in 7 hours and 34 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.154185022026432,
            5.6351338132896895,
            3.1919572070949482,
            8.88978102518562
        ],
        "answer": 5.154185022026432
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 43000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 71000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            742,
            60,
            162,
            0.606
        ],
        "answer": 0.606
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            10,
            -25,
            15,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 92 miles in 9 hours and 8 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.895313332904511,
            3.2446868903397856,
            10.072992700729927,
            1.175469244382605
        ],
        "answer": 10.072992700729927
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 4 cake , how many cake can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            4,
            10,
            14,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 19 years old in the year 1296.In his greatest win, he looted 329185167 of 7985282802 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1277,
            1486,
            1317,
            1870
        ],
        "answer": 1277
    },
    {
        "question": "Krishna wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 37cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            16,
            39,
            43,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mohammed wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 24cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            18,
            31,
            40,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Morales wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 19cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            3,
            30,
            43,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 11.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            31.6,
            491,
            105,
            295
        ],
        "answer": 31.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Reed wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 9.781 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 6.12,
        "options": [
            61.2,
            6.12,
            9.781,
            6.22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jenkins wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 6.848 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 2.58,
        "options": [
            6.848,
            2.58,
            2.68,
            25.8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 46 ohms and 11 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            46,
            11,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            6,
            12,
            1,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 25 chair, 99 fan, 3 snail, and 5 trees? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            104,
            54,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gonzales wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 4.04 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 1.18,
        "options": [
            1.28,
            4.04,
            11.799999999999999,
            1.18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            25,
            -25,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            2,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 pair of shoes, 19 bed, 60 tubelight, 5 cockroaches, and 15 cat? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            31,
            65,
            21,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 42 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            86,
            42,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 86000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 669000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            0.129,
            558,
            511,
            928
        ],
        "answer": 0.129
    },
    {
        "question": "Rivera wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 3.447 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 1.68,
        "options": [
            16.8,
            1.78,
            3.447,
            1.68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            0,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 9 men, 8 women, 8 children of less than 10 years, 3 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            103,
            28,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "King wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 31cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            18,
            14,
            8,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 75 miles in 1 hours and 37 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.346302737126567,
            9.468740055427283,
            46.391752577319586,
            5.90500493227434
        ],
        "answer": 46.391752577319586
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 35 ohms and 30 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            5,
            12,
            1050,
            0,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anaya wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 9.778 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 1.08,
        "options": [
            1.1800000000000002,
            10.8,
            9.778,
            1.08
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 40 miles in 1 hours and 40 minutes?",
        "options": [
            38.4,
            9.727657662268426,
            8.610673506047217,
            6.566238262718359
        ],
        "answer": 38.4
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            -25,
            25,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Hughes wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 6.0 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 4.65,
        "options": [
            46.5,
            6.0,
            4.75,
            4.65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 14 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            4,
            -11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 13 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a man eat?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            13,
            19,
            32,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jenkins wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 36cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            38,
            33,
            30,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -11,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "Patterson wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 13cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            7,
            2,
            12,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 bed, 33 cycles, 47 table, 12 snail, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            85,
            59,
            37,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            1,
            5,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reynolds wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 9cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            2,
            5,
            14,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stephens wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 15cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            5,
            16,
            38,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 11 years old in the year 1298.In his greatest win, he looted 648490272 of 3087208829 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many of them are transferred to Jordan city??",
        "options": [
            3087208829,
            3735699101,
            648490272,
            2438718557
        ],
        "answer": 648490272
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 17 miles in 6 hours and 24 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.65625,
            4.671822359461402,
            7.675214557632633,
            8.26608811770874
        ],
        "answer": 2.65625
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            -1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            14,
            13,
            5,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ananya wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 7.455 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 3.88,
        "options": [
            3.98,
            7.455,
            38.8,
            3.88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 84. When the sun is at 55 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            85,
            100,
            53,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 7 feet by 9 feet?",
        "options": [
            8015,
            9072,
            3720,
            9299
        ],
        "answer": 9072
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            9,
            1,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Evans wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 10cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            5,
            14,
            26,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 14 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            14,
            27,
            2,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 11000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 18000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            700,
            4,
            0.611,
            434
        ],
        "answer": 0.611
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 tubelight, 89 empty boxes, 24 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 7 plants? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            133,
            7,
            129,
            133
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 41.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            164.6,
            346,
            350,
            444
        ],
        "answer": 164.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Woods wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 28cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            39,
            9,
            40,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            7,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 flower vase, 90 pair of shoes, 18 refrigerator, 3 cockroaches, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            112,
            63,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Coleman wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 5cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            12,
            11,
            16,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            24,
            2,
            10,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kabir wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 29cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            18,
            20,
            32,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            -27,
            22,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Hernandez wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 19cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            42,
            19,
            33,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            -27,
            22,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 broom, 20 pair of shoes, 43 sofa, 11 cat, and 13 crows? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            85,
            53,
            80,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            7,
            6,
            1,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Murray wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 12cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            16,
            29,
            23,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Veer wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 28cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            5,
            8,
            43,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 14 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            14,
            20,
            34,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Collins wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 6cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            13,
            17,
            11,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Advik earns $18 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $4 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Advik was paid $3835, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            192,
            319,
            436,
            354
        ],
        "answer": 192
    },
    {
        "question": "Shanaya wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 32cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            8,
            35,
            36,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 17 miles in 3 hours and 49 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.070496731075425,
            4.454148471615721,
            9.30859347665563,
            6.193082321268124
        ],
        "answer": 4.454148471615721
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 35 miles in 7 hours and 10 minutes?",
        "options": [
            3.030900366320749,
            8.817345191863634,
            9.935634710111653,
            0.13023255813953488
        ],
        "answer": 0.13023255813953488
    },
    {
        "question": "Iraa wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 3.681 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 1.01,
        "options": [
            1.11,
            10.1,
            1.01,
            3.681
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 8 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            12,
            6,
            11,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 8 feet by 6 feet?",
        "options": [
            8224,
            8795,
            7946,
            6912
        ],
        "answer": 6912
    },
    {
        "question": "Powell began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 328,
        "options": [
            0,
            328,
            329,
            330
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            19,
            7,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "Mason wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 35cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            5,
            41,
            45,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            4,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 42 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            86,
            44,
            9,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 23 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            23,
            29,
            52,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 table, 58 empty boxes, 12 flower vase, 5 fungi spots, and 1 trees? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            73,
            62,
            63,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 21 lemons , how many lemons can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            21,
            27,
            48,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Torres wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 38cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            42,
            42,
            33,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 38 ohms and 48 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 24 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            50,
            1824,
            24,
            48,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            5,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -19,
            18,
            19,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 sofa, 83 broom, 23 pair of shoes, 13 snail, and 12 fungi spots? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            107,
            374,
            352,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Clark wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 17cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            24,
            45,
            16,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nichols began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 375,
        "options": [
            377,
            0,
            376,
            375
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 5 ohms and 20 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            25,
            8,
            20,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            12,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            5,
            -25,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 33 ohms and 9 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 1 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            9,
            33,
            1,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 bed, 43 broom, 43 refrigerator, 10 algae spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            22,
            53,
            54,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarush began counting from 0. She skip-counted by nine's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 126,
        "options": [
            128,
            127,
            126,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            2,
            3,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $24 to the charity and a total of $14660 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            115,
            209,
            591,
            610
        ],
        "answer": 610
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 88 pair of shoes, 94 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 5 plants? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            90,
            8,
            7,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 24 tubelight, 86 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 11 crows? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            89,
            37,
            14,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shanaya wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 35cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            3,
            42,
            3,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            1,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 11 watermelon , how many watermelon can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            11,
            15,
            26,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 21 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            6,
            11,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -19,
            18,
            19,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 7000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 892000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            867,
            202,
            7.848,
            397
        ],
        "answer": 7.848
    },
    {
        "question": "Ishaan began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 168,
        "options": [
            168,
            170,
            0,
            169
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 28 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            28,
            72,
            6,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            22,
            14,
            12,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 35.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            281.4,
            370,
            283,
            366
        ],
        "answer": 281.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 6.264 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 3.85,
        "options": [
            6.264,
            3.85,
            3.95,
            38.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Meyer wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 34cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            29,
            27,
            45,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 98000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 81000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            474,
            331,
            347,
            1209.877
        ],
        "answer": 1209.877
    },
    {
        "question": "Lopez wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 9.742 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 4.49,
        "options": [
            4.49,
            4.59,
            9.742,
            44.900000000000006
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 39cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            29,
            41,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 8 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            19,
            3,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Edwards began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 456,
        "options": [
            0,
            456,
            458,
            457
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Grant wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 7.058 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 5.98,
        "options": [
            59.800000000000004,
            6.08,
            7.058,
            5.98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            3,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            8,
            2,
            9,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 9 men, 8 women, 5 children of less than 10 years, 3 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            103,
            25,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ananya wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 18cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            13,
            27,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 83000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 211000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            190,
            987,
            381,
            393.365
        ],
        "answer": 393.365
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 6.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            129,
            232,
            400,
            49.7
        ],
        "answer": 49.7
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $38 to the charity and a total of $15528 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            50,
            955,
            235,
            408
        ],
        "answer": 408
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 37 ohms and 38 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            38,
            75,
            37,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aditya wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 9.635 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 7.99,
        "options": [
            9.635,
            79.9,
            8.09,
            7.99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stevens wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 9.887 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 6.88,
        "options": [
            6.9799999999999995,
            6.88,
            68.8,
            9.887
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Crawford wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 5.655 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 4.44,
        "options": [
            4.54,
            5.655,
            44.400000000000006,
            4.44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Akshara began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 240,
        "options": [
            241,
            242,
            0,
            240
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hill earns $17 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $2 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Hill was paid $2987, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            38,
            167,
            336,
            190
        ],
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 cycles, 75 bed, 7 sofa, 2 snail, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            9,
            83,
            84,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 50 ohms and 20 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            1000,
            70,
            9,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $66 to the charity and a total of $10335 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            969,
            315,
            156,
            771
        ],
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "question": "Wright wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 6.081 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 2.84,
        "options": [
            28.4,
            6.081,
            2.94,
            2.84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            7,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Pierce began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            52,
            0,
            51,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Garcia began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 192,
        "options": [
            0,
            193,
            192,
            194
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dixon began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 340,
        "options": [
            0,
            340,
            341,
            342
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            9,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 couch, 63 tubelight, 44 empty boxes, 14 dog, and 15 people? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            9,
            106,
            144
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            10,
            23,
            6,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brooks wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 13cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            5,
            3,
            15,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 cycles, 77 empty boxes, 12 bed, 4 human beings, and 11 cat? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            108,
            56,
            101,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hunt wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 4.713 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 3.56,
        "options": [
            3.56,
            4.713,
            3.66,
            35.6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -24,
            24,
            4,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 flower vase, 52 mat, 10 couch, 1 cockroaches, and 3 human beings? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            5,
            11,
            57,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Murphy wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 36cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            34,
            25,
            45,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 mat, 63 chair, 28 fan, 12 trees, and 1 cat? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            100,
            99,
            71,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            8,
            22,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -28,
            28,
            22,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 10 watermelon , how many watermelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            10,
            6,
            16,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            3,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 9 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            9072,
            1975,
            8037,
            4183
        ],
        "answer": 9072
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            4,
            5,
            11,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 28 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            4,
            1232,
            7,
            72,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 38 ohms and 48 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1824,
            4,
            1,
            0,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 empty boxes, 73 flower vase, 53 mat, 10 fungi spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 93,
        "options": [
            257,
            93,
            207,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hernandez wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 31cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            33,
            3,
            9,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $28 to the charity and a total of $10032 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            271,
            168,
            358,
            959
        ],
        "answer": 358
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            -25,
            25,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 80000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 677000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            5,
            817,
            118168.39,
            795
        ],
        "answer": 118168.39
    },
    {
        "question": "Rice wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 24cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            12,
            27,
            38,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 18 apples , how many apples can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            18,
            24,
            42,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 tubelight, 43 couch, 65 table, 4 people, and 9 plants? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 117,
        "options": [
            69,
            118,
            117,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rivera began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 560,
        "options": [
            562,
            560,
            0,
            561
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 cycles, 75 bed, 7 sofa, 2 snail, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            87,
            93,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 10 lemons , how many lemons can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            10,
            18,
            28,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mitchell began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 425,
        "options": [
            425,
            0,
            427,
            426
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 17cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            18,
            10,
            18,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 mat, 63 chair, 28 fan, 12 trees, and 1 cat? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            14,
            40,
            71,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Angel wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 16cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            37,
            40,
            38,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            16,
            3,
            4,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hall earns $18 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $5 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Hall was paid $3984, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            194,
            347,
            393,
            376
        ],
        "answer": 194
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 36 ohms and 28 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 18 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            28,
            18,
            64,
            45,
            1008
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Henderson began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            89,
            88,
            90,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            -25,
            25,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Morgan wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 40cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            7,
            12,
            3,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ramos wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 15cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            27,
            17,
            14,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Smith began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 448,
        "options": [
            0,
            449,
            448,
            450
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gomez began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 276,
        "options": [
            278,
            277,
            276,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            5,
            -25,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Saanvi wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 4.018 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 1.37,
        "options": [
            1.37,
            1.4700000000000002,
            4.018,
            13.700000000000001
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 26 ohms and 15 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            24,
            390,
            41,
            15,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 8 feet by 2 feet?",
        "options": [
            9148,
            2304,
            5488,
            7368
        ],
        "answer": 2304
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 22 lemons , how many lemons can a man eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            22,
            24,
            46,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 15000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 688000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            48,
            167,
            21802.326,
            963
        ],
        "answer": 21802.326
    },
    {
        "question": "Cox wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 13cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            10,
            17,
            11,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            20,
            -23,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Prisha wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 31cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            28,
            3,
            7,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayes wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 13cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            7,
            35,
            5,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Schmidt wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 6.521 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 5.42,
        "options": [
            6.521,
            5.42,
            54.2,
            5.52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 25 chair, 99 fan, 3 snail, and 5 trees? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 116,
        "options": [
            116,
            131,
            129,
            130
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elliott wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 14cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            21,
            33,
            31,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 40 ohms and 42 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            82,
            6,
            1680,
            7,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 46 ohms and 11 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            57,
            46,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 7 feet by 6 feet?",
        "options": [
            6700,
            6048,
            2452,
            4403
        ],
        "answer": 6048
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $56 to the charity and a total of $6068 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            108,
            865,
            765,
            182
        ],
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $62 to the charity and a total of $19924 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            788,
            942,
            886,
            321
        ],
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 14 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            4,
            -11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "Aditya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 240,
        "options": [
            240,
            0,
            242,
            241
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $66 to the charity and a total of $9012 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            982,
            905,
            136,
            286
        ],
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 6 feet by 4 feet?",
        "options": [
            3456,
            910,
            9405,
            5642
        ],
        "answer": 3456
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 13 ohms and 25 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            38,
            0,
            10,
            325
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 42 miles in 10 hours and 14 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.06840390879478828,
            9.320920716549736,
            6.2980167616413425,
            6.225907661762472
        ],
        "answer": 0.06840390879478828
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 flower vase, 43 sofa, 86 mat, 9 fungi spots, and 3 dog? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            13,
            95,
            12,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            2,
            -27,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 88 pair of shoes, 94 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 5 plants? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 184,
        "options": [
            90,
            184,
            185,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fernandez earns $9 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $3 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Fernandez was paid $1078, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            47,
            60,
            114,
            66
        ],
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "Prisha earns $17 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $2 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Prisha was paid $4342, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            285,
            239,
            317,
            453
        ],
        "answer": 239
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            -25,
            25,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            0,
            4,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wallace began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 204,
        "options": [
            204,
            205,
            206,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 37 tubelight, 38 cycles, 12 crows, and 10 snail? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            23,
            22,
            47,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bennett wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 28cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            35,
            18,
            5,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            2,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 25 miles in 10 hours and 7 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.080563761298521,
            6.306640303076543,
            9.689773372173923,
            3.9538714991762767
        ],
        "answer": 3.9538714991762767
    },
    {
        "question": "Romero wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 33cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            2,
            34,
            19,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gray wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 21cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            9,
            2,
            41,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 7 men, 3 women, 7 children of less than 10 years, 6 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            114,
            23,
            0,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "West wants to put a house in a street.The street is 6.273 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 4.94,
        "options": [
            5.04,
            49.400000000000006,
            6.273,
            4.94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 1years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Friday",
            "Saturday",
            "tuesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            2,
            10,
            11,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            -27,
            22,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 68 grapes , how many grapes can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            68,
            69,
            137,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jackson wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 7.906 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 5.56,
        "options": [
            5.659999999999999,
            7.906,
            55.599999999999994,
            5.56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 flower vase, 33 table, 84 cycles, 15 pigeons, and 8 human beings? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            35,
            44,
            129
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 sofa, 84 couch, 55 pair of shoes, 11 fungi spots, and 12 human beings? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            163,
            147,
            168,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 36.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            225,
            242,
            348,
            216.2
        ],
        "answer": 216.2
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            18,
            14,
            13,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Martin began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 203,
        "options": [
            203,
            0,
            205,
            204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            -1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            14,
            11,
            25,
            -25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 21 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            6,
            11,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 82000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 765000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            704,
            724,
            440,
            107189.542
        ],
        "answer": 107189.542
    },
    {
        "question": "Palmer wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 4.678 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 2.4,
        "options": [
            2.4,
            24.0,
            4.678,
            2.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            19,
            7,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 empty boxes, 83 flower vase, 50 broom, 7 trees, and 9 dog? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            160,
            4,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            10,
            12,
            11,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            -27,
            22,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 50 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            2200,
            3,
            1,
            0,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 9 cake , how many cake can a man eat?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            9,
            8,
            17,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 chair, 39 couch, 5 bed, 13 people, and 11 algae spots? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            57,
            39,
            71,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 69 broom, 92 mat, 1 cockroaches, and 8 cat? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            109,
            3,
            75,
            164
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 empty boxes, 83 flower vase, 50 broom, 7 trees, and 9 dog? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 148,
        "options": [
            149,
            57,
            98,
            148
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            1,
            6,
            5,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 broom, 33 refrigerator, 41 pair of shoes, 8 cat, and 11 human beings? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            47,
            20,
            49,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 49.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            195.0,
            222,
            226,
            457
        ],
        "answer": 195.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Richardson wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 22cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            20,
            42,
            36,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            5,
            -25,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            25,
            -25,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 37 ohms and 38 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            38,
            75,
            37,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $56 to the charity and a total of $12795 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            228,
            710,
            516,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            25,
            13,
            12,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Campbell increased from 692 per month to 882 per month while the salary of Long increased from 319 to 876 and of Aayan increased from 865 to 967 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Aayan",
        "options": [
            "Campbell",
            "Long",
            "Aayan",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 38 miles in 6 hours and 60 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.09047619047619047,
            8.397202209949953,
            7.087375438197422,
            9.623713026081353
        ],
        "answer": 0.09047619047619047
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 sofa, 84 couch, 55 pair of shoes, 11 fungi spots, and 12 human beings? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            81,
            84,
            129,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            15,
            2,
            3,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 192,
        "options": [
            0,
            194,
            192,
            193
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gutierrez wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 14cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            5,
            10,
            30,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 chair, 26 pair of shoes, 88 cycles, 15 cockroaches, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            23,
            32,
            103,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 cycles, 77 empty boxes, 12 bed, 4 human beings, and 11 cat? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            95,
            94,
            16,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 fan, 33 empty boxes, 30 tubelight, 2 dog, and 12 cat? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            15,
            32,
            44,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -28,
            28,
            22,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 13 ohms and 45 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            58,
            10,
            13,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            4,
            10,
            22,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 18 lemons , how many lemons can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            18,
            30,
            48,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -11,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 9 sofa, 93 couch, 11 people, and 7 cockroaches? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            105,
            38,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 43 ohms and 30 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            1290,
            73,
            0,
            10,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gray wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 21cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            5,
            7,
            3,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            3,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            -27,
            22,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $44 to the charity and a total of $18428 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            603,
            986,
            915,
            418
        ],
        "answer": 418
    },
    {
        "question": "Freeman wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 7.52 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 2.79,
        "options": [
            7.52,
            27.9,
            2.89,
            2.79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 14 ohms and 22 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            36,
            22,
            14,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 19 ohms and 36 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            6,
            55,
            0,
            684
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 14 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            41,
            9,
            14,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            7,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Turner began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            79,
            78,
            0,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 16 chocolates , how many chocolates can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            16,
            7,
            23,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 43.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            407,
            387.3,
            435,
            424
        ],
        "answer": 387.3
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 flower vase, 90 pair of shoes, 18 refrigerator, 3 cockroaches, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            87,
            17,
            132,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 50 fan, 58 sofa, 4 cat, and 3 dog? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            336,
            379,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 chair, 26 pair of shoes, 88 cycles, 15 cockroaches, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            140,
            125,
            128,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 58 miles in 8 hours and 41 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.64722761765573,
            0.11132437619961612,
            1.1089938287574306,
            7.812716813830786
        ],
        "answer": 0.11132437619961612
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Sunday and returns to the bank 3years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Wednesday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "Thursday",
            "Thursday",
            "tuesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 25.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            378,
            428,
            311,
            199.6
        ],
        "answer": 199.6
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 table, 7 refrigerator, 53 bed, 2 human beings, and 15 snail? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            19,
            4,
            66,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 empty boxes, 60 cycles, 58 refrigerator, 1 pigeons, and 11 trees? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            13,
            70,
            12,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Owens wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 15cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            28,
            30,
            43,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            7,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcdonald wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 29cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            21,
            34,
            22,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 6 ohms and 32 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            8,
            38,
            32,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 29 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            47,
            29,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -11,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 sofa, 61 table, 63 bed, 8 snail, and 10 fungi spots? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            32,
            134,
            3,
            124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 30.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            370,
            213,
            92.4,
            123
        ],
        "answer": 92.4
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 43.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            440,
            486,
            382.7,
            476
        ],
        "answer": 382.7
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 24 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            0,
            43,
            8,
            456,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            9,
            2,
            19,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Phillips wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 27cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            21,
            39,
            34,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 320,
        "options": [
            322,
            0,
            321,
            320
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 160 grapes , how many grapes can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            160,
            84,
            244,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 17 lemons , how many lemons can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            17,
            23,
            40,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            10,
            -25,
            15,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 12 ohms and 49 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            10,
            61,
            588
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            5,
            -25,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 20 miles in 6 hours and 1 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.86275154007431,
            3.3240997229916895,
            6.544627666919092,
            4.993250537770052
        ],
        "answer": 3.3240997229916895
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 48 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            7,
            0,
            864,
            9,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 36 ohms and 39 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            1404,
            6,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            5,
            -26,
            21,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 8 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            8,
            6,
            14,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 71 grapes , how many grapes can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 167,
        "options": [
            71,
            167,
            238,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gonzales wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 31cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            12,
            37,
            26,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Howard wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 36cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            9,
            40,
            5,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stone earns $18 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $2 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Stone was paid $2534, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            300,
            136,
            126,
            432
        ],
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            5,
            -26,
            21,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Ferguson wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 37cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            40,
            11,
            37,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            21,
            9,
            0,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            27,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 10.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            59.6,
            343,
            144,
            67
        ],
        "answer": 59.6
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 28 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            72,
            22,
            1232,
            9,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 52 miles in 9 hours and 59 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.376201090069188,
            9.676527561540086,
            8.642745659236843,
            5.208681135225375
        ],
        "answer": 5.208681135225375
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 11000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 231000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            911,
            332,
            51,
            47619.048
        ],
        "answer": 47619.048
    },
    {
        "question": "Reynolds wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 8.707 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 2.66,
        "options": [
            8.707,
            2.66,
            2.7600000000000002,
            26.6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 bed, 57 table, 12 fan, 13 fungi spots, and 9 people? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            67,
            45,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            4,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 8 ohms and 12 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            20,
            10,
            12,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 32000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 322000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            442,
            99.379,
            50,
            995
        ],
        "answer": 99.379
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            0,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 8 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            13,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 27.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            484,
            169.6,
            360,
            373
        ],
        "answer": 169.6
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 48 ohms and 48 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 13 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            2304,
            48,
            32,
            96,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 tubelight, 43 couch, 65 table, 4 people, and 9 plants? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 114,
        "options": [
            114,
            0,
            133,
            329
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 flower vase, 95 pair of shoes, 31 sofa, 11 dog, and 6 snail? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            17,
            18,
            42,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 14 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            30,
            15,
            14,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kabir began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 315,
        "options": [
            317,
            315,
            316,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ellis wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 8.548 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 4.61,
        "options": [
            4.71,
            4.61,
            46.1,
            8.548
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Siya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 203,
        "options": [
            203,
            0,
            205,
            204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gibson began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 140,
        "options": [
            140,
            142,
            0,
            141
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 18 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            24,
            12,
            -24
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            2,
            -27,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Cox wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 24cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            24,
            2,
            45,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 sofa, 83 broom, 23 pair of shoes, 13 snail, and 12 fungi spots? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            127,
            105,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 67 pair of shoes, 94 bed, 9 cockroaches, and 13 crows? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            71,
            22,
            23,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Moreno wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 16cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            6,
            40,
            13,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            10,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Sullivan increased from 840 per month to 918 per month while the salary of Herrera increased from 763 to 789 and of Hunt increased from 300 to 787 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Hunt",
        "options": [
            "Sullivan",
            "Herrera",
            "Hunt",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            8,
            2,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 28 watermelon , how many watermelon can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            28,
            16,
            44,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 73. When the sun is at 60 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            98,
            1,
            98,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            20,
            -23,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 30.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            425,
            414,
            264.0,
            316
        ],
        "answer": 264.0
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 bed, 43 broom, 43 refrigerator, 10 algae spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            71,
            172,
            0,
            197
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            4,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Diya wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 6cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            21,
            16,
            16,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 67 pair of shoes, 94 bed, 9 cockroaches, and 13 crows? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            71,
            22,
            23,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            10,
            5,
            1,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 29 sofa, 61 tubelight, 4 snail, and 12 dog? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            12,
            108,
            105,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 49 ohms and 47 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            8,
            96,
            47,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 30 flower vase, 24 sofa, 2 plants, and 2 dog? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            43,
            67,
            26,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 67 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 1/6 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            41,
            84,
            83,
            11.17
        ],
        "answer": 11.17
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 22 lemons , how many lemons can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            22,
            25,
            47,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bell wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 25cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            6,
            28,
            14,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 flower vase, 52 mat, 10 couch, 1 cockroaches, and 3 human beings? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            52,
            20,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -24,
            24,
            4,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Mcdonald increased from 971 per month to 972 per month while the salary of Jordan increased from 313 to 966 and of Nelson increased from 613 to 953 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Nelson",
        "options": [
            "Mcdonald",
            "Jordan",
            "Nelson",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 22 watermelon , how many watermelon can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            22,
            20,
            42,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Chavez wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 17cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            21,
            11,
            2,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 36 ohms and 28 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            64,
            9,
            36,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 1 cake , how many cake can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            1,
            4,
            5,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 67 pair of shoes, 94 bed, 9 cockroaches, and 13 crows? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            172,
            176,
            44,
            167
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 9 feet by 1 feet?",
        "options": [
            978,
            1296,
            5491,
            6632
        ],
        "answer": 1296
    },
    {
        "question": "Iraa began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 574,
        "options": [
            575,
            0,
            574,
            576
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 flower vase, 43 sofa, 86 mat, 9 fungi spots, and 3 dog? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            54,
            134,
            132,
            132
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 82. When the sun is at 30 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 98,
        "options": [
            98,
            10,
            3,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tucker earns $14 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $4 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Tucker was paid $3377, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            198,
            209,
            352,
            287
        ],
        "answer": 209
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 14 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            4,
            -11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 30 apples , how many apples can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            30,
            17,
            47,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 31.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            385,
            326,
            423,
            275.8
        ],
        "answer": 275.8
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            2,
            -27,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 refrigerator, 5 bed, 45 couch, 8 pigeons, and 7 dog? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            20,
            66,
            65,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sullivan began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            122,
            121,
            120,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anaya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 296,
        "options": [
            297,
            0,
            296,
            298
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Barnes earns $6 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $5 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Barnes was paid $1905, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            218,
            445,
            126,
            347
        ],
        "answer": 218
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Cunningham increased from 368 per month to 920 per month while the salary of Owens increased from 318 to 671 and of Robinson increased from 778 to 852 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Robinson",
        "options": [
            "Cunningham",
            "Owens",
            "Robinson",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 30 flower vase, 24 sofa, 2 plants, and 2 dog? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            43,
            26,
            5,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Monday and returns to the bank 5years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "Saturday",
            "Thursday",
            "tuesday",
            "Wednesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            25,
            -25,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 7 apples , how many apples can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            7,
            20,
            27,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Freeman earns $7 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $4 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Freeman was paid $2325, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            434,
            247,
            52,
            217
        ],
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 10 cake , how many cake can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            10,
            5,
            15,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 60 miles in 8 hours and 3 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.380735006571926,
            4.636688205081613,
            0.19875776397515527,
            5.454256454956863
        ],
        "answer": 0.19875776397515527
    },
    {
        "question": "Hunt wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 22cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            45,
            23,
            39,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Smith wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 6.814 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 4.87,
        "options": [
            6.814,
            4.87,
            4.97,
            48.7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 flower vase, 52 mat, 10 couch, 1 cockroaches, and 3 human beings? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            68,
            67,
            57,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dunn wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 14cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            26,
            24,
            21,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 20000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 931000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            943,
            21.482,
            205,
            584
        ],
        "answer": 21.482
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 bed, 33 cycles, 47 table, 12 snail, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            85,
            59,
            37,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            19,
            7,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $20 to the charity and a total of $7480 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            374,
            687,
            659,
            998
        ],
        "answer": 374
    },
    {
        "question": "Aditya wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 39cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            7,
            35,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 chair, 96 pair of shoes, 13 bed, 1 crows, and 5 human beings? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            124,
            127,
            22,
            124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            10,
            3,
            4,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 empty boxes, 60 cycles, 58 refrigerator, 1 pigeons, and 11 trees? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 128,
        "options": [
            70,
            129,
            128,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            18,
            10,
            9,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 40 cycles, 8 fan, 7 human beings, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            51,
            0,
            394,
            116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            5,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            5,
            -25,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 cycles, 77 empty boxes, 12 bed, 4 human beings, and 11 cat? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            74,
            93,
            12,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 37.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            354,
            82.2,
            306,
            382
        ],
        "answer": 82.2
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 20000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 536000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            755,
            0.037,
            886,
            287
        ],
        "answer": 0.037
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            -27,
            22,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 21 chocolates , how many chocolates can a man eat?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            21,
            13,
            34,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bailey began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 384,
        "options": [
            0,
            385,
            384,
            386
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            5,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 8 lemons , how many lemons can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            8,
            23,
            31,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nichols wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 8.127 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 1.53,
        "options": [
            1.6300000000000001,
            8.127,
            15.3,
            1.53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 6 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            6,
            11,
            17,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 22 apples , how many apples can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            22,
            29,
            51,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            2,
            -27,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            14,
            11,
            25,
            -25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Mohammed wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 7cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            31,
            19,
            3,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 1 cake , how many cake can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            1,
            10,
            11,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            -27,
            22,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            5,
            6,
            1,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 bed, 43 broom, 43 refrigerator, 10 algae spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 97,
        "options": [
            53,
            97,
            98,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shaurya wants to put a house in a street.The street is 7.147 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 4.78,
        "options": [
            4.78,
            7.147,
            4.88,
            47.800000000000004
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 50 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 1 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            44,
            50,
            1,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            25,
            -25,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Garcia wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 3.553 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 1.41,
        "options": [
            14.1,
            3.553,
            1.51,
            1.41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 37 tubelight, 38 cycles, 12 crows, and 10 snail? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            47,
            23,
            50,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ritvik wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 9.78 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 4.81,
        "options": [
            4.909999999999999,
            48.099999999999994,
            4.81,
            9.78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 94 miles in 6 hours and 26 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.309039539719523,
            7.118036714554303,
            7.62204431413419,
            0.3896373056994819
        ],
        "answer": 0.3896373056994819
    },
    {
        "question": "Schmidt wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 8cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            13,
            22,
            12,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gibson wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 15cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            22,
            13,
            25,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 33 ohms and 44 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            44,
            77,
            7,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Olson increased from 818 per month to 867 per month while the salary of Aaryan increased from 790 to 888 and of Pierce increased from 633 to 987 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Pierce",
        "options": [
            "Olson",
            "Aaryan",
            "Pierce",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 13 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            28,
            25,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Arjun wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 39cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            19,
            37,
            41,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 20 chocolates , how many chocolates can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            20,
            6,
            26,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 8 feet by 2 feet?",
        "options": [
            8771,
            4285,
            8654,
            2304
        ],
        "answer": 2304
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 88 pair of shoes, 94 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 5 plants? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            90,
            7,
            96,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Black wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 25cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            42,
            21,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -11,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 8 ohms and 12 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 25 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            25,
            96,
            53,
            20,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Navya wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 23cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            26,
            3,
            14,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Harrison wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 20cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            42,
            19,
            33,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -11,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 17 ohms and 7 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            17,
            8,
            7,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            15,
            1,
            10,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 10 cake , how many cake can a man eat?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            10,
            4,
            14,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            1,
            9,
            8,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 13 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            28,
            25,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 broom, 33 refrigerator, 41 pair of shoes, 8 cat, and 11 human beings? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            88,
            89,
            49,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 fan, 33 empty boxes, 30 tubelight, 2 dog, and 12 cat? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            56,
            30,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 29000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 589000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            107,
            178,
            30,
            49.236
        ],
        "answer": 49.236
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 21 chocolates , how many chocolates can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            21,
            24,
            45,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            3,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            12,
            5,
            6,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 29 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            522,
            47,
            12,
            5,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 13 watermelon , how many watermelon can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            13,
            15,
            28,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 14 lemons , how many lemons can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            14,
            6,
            20,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 88 miles in 6 hours and 38 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.695412769243216,
            13.266331658291458,
            3.8898951083197955,
            5.586213198143106
        ],
        "answer": 13.266331658291458
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 13 lemons , how many lemons can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            13,
            27,
            40,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 69 broom, 92 mat, 1 cockroaches, and 8 cat? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            93,
            9,
            10,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 flower vase, 33 table, 84 cycles, 15 pigeons, and 8 human beings? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 111,
        "options": [
            111,
            135,
            149,
            136
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 36 ohms and 39 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            7,
            39,
            75,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 refrigerator, 22 fan, 97 cycles, 3 algae spots, and 13 snail? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 122,
        "options": [
            123,
            122,
            25,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnav wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 15cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            26,
            6,
            31,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Sunday and returns to the bank 1years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Monday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "Monday",
            "Sunday",
            "Thursday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Darsh wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 25cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            5,
            27,
            19,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 28. When the sun is at 65 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            37,
            76,
            45,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 40 cycles, 8 fan, 7 human beings, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            49,
            19,
            15,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            4,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 sofa, 61 table, 63 bed, 8 snail, and 10 fungi spots? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            19,
            62,
            71,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            7,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -19,
            18,
            19,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 cycles, 75 bed, 7 sofa, 2 snail, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            9,
            76,
            16,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 chair, 7 tubelight, 2 bed, 9 algae spots, and 12 dog? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            16,
            27,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Burns wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 22cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            2,
            35,
            28,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            19,
            7,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1209.In his greatest win, he looted 727190034 of 3565692525 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1371,
            1673,
            1205,
            1192
        ],
        "answer": 1192
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $52 to the charity and a total of $13668 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            492,
            262,
            161,
            742
        ],
        "answer": 262
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 pair of shoes, 67 chair, 8 bed, 12 plants, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            86,
            85,
            20,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 117 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 2/8 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            21,
            29.25,
            96,
            58
        ],
        "answer": 29.25
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 26 lemons , how many lemons can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            26,
            18,
            44,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jordan wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 8.441 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 4.16,
        "options": [
            41.6,
            4.26,
            8.441,
            4.16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Green wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 4.248 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 1.31,
        "options": [
            13.100000000000001,
            1.4100000000000001,
            4.248,
            1.31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            5,
            -16,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 26 ohms and 5 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 21 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            31,
            130,
            21,
            5,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 empty boxes, 73 flower vase, 53 mat, 10 fungi spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            148,
            55,
            149,
            150
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 13 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            2,
            27,
            3,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Graham wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 7.632 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 1.17,
        "options": [
            7.632,
            11.7,
            1.27,
            1.17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 pair of shoes, 19 bed, 60 tubelight, 5 cockroaches, and 15 cat? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 91,
        "options": [
            91,
            31,
            92,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 chair, 96 pair of shoes, 13 bed, 1 crows, and 5 human beings? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 122,
        "options": [
            122,
            14,
            123,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 12.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            89,
            477,
            33.8,
            338
        ],
        "answer": 33.8
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 9 men, 5 women, 5 children of less than 10 years, 4 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            118,
            23,
            0,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nguyen wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 23cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            2,
            34,
            34,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -24,
            24,
            4,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "Young wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 3.992 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 2.24,
        "options": [
            3.992,
            22.400000000000002,
            2.24,
            2.3400000000000003
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 30 flower vase, 24 sofa, 2 plants, and 2 dog? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            37,
            70,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1447.In his greatest win, he looted 773777279 of 1076331660 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1439,
            1783,
            1432,
            1645
        ],
        "answer": 1432
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 24.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            311,
            234,
            381,
            218.4
        ],
        "answer": 218.4
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 10 men, 4 women, 3 children of less than 10 years, 8 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            113,
            25,
            0,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            5,
            -16,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 12000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 642000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            840,
            590,
            436,
            18.692
        ],
        "answer": 18.692
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 12 ohms and 49 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            61,
            49,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 chair, 96 pair of shoes, 13 bed, 1 crows, and 5 human beings? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            7,
            14,
            6,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -11,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 29.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            170,
            300,
            60.4,
            197
        ],
        "answer": 60.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Washington wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 9.915 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 4.34,
        "options": [
            4.4399999999999995,
            4.34,
            43.4,
            9.915
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hill wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 19cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            32,
            21,
            18,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mills wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 6.695 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 2.34,
        "options": [
            23.4,
            6.695,
            2.34,
            2.44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 14000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 755000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            266,
            0.019,
            379,
            508
        ],
        "answer": 0.019
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            2,
            9,
            10,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1490.In his greatest win, he looted 277094937 of 6464511498 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1475,
            1770,
            1760,
            1677
        ],
        "answer": 1475
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 94 miles in 2 hours and 18 minutes?",
        "options": [
            3.473018970237028,
            8.805115577565816,
            5.559484248298281,
            1.0898550724637681
        ],
        "answer": 1.0898550724637681
    },
    {
        "question": "Jordan wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 37cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            44,
            44,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shaurya wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 30cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            42,
            38,
            20,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            4,
            5,
            0,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 26 ohms and 15 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            390,
            0,
            8,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Marshall wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 12cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            39,
            24,
            36,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            5,
            -26,
            21,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Castillo increased from 402 per month to 533 per month while the salary of Rodriguez increased from 964 to 974 and of Mendoza increased from 575 to 697 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Mendoza",
        "options": [
            "Castillo",
            "Rodriguez",
            "Mendoza",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 chair, 39 couch, 5 bed, 13 people, and 11 algae spots? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            50,
            18,
            55,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 20.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            322,
            140.9,
            316,
            363
        ],
        "answer": 140.9
    },
    {
        "question": "Price wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 14cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            22,
            23,
            13,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rodriguez wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 37cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            23,
            45,
            43,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            9,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $20 to the charity and a total of $5646 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            231,
            282,
            940,
            398
        ],
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            5,
            -16,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "Clark wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 31cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            36,
            6,
            36,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            27,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 176 grapes , how many grapes can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            176,
            88,
            264,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lee wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 11cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            31,
            9,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 17 miles in 9 hours and 10 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.04945454545454546,
            9.392616844202541,
            7.421966557681094,
            7.634152278836186
        ],
        "answer": 0.04945454545454546
    },
    {
        "question": "Jackson wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 23cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            14,
            9,
            23,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Clark wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 6.714 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 1.67,
        "options": [
            6.714,
            1.67,
            1.77,
            16.7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $60 to the charity and a total of $14001 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            164,
            233,
            626,
            833
        ],
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 flower vase, 90 pair of shoes, 18 refrigerator, 3 cockroaches, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            100,
            19,
            21,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Price wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 15cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            6,
            21,
            25,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 43.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            184,
            177.4,
            298,
            457
        ],
        "answer": 177.4
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 chair, 39 couch, 5 bed, 13 people, and 11 algae spots? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            0,
            234,
            350
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cunningham wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 8cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            29,
            16,
            38,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 3 men, 4 women, 8 children of less than 10 years, 7 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            110,
            22,
            0,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 8 feet by 8 feet?",
        "options": [
            8421,
            9216,
            8547,
            4050
        ],
        "answer": 9216
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 15 miles in 8 hours and 48 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.229772718418584,
            3.486124741924454,
            4.006572610701554,
            2.7272727272727275
        ],
        "answer": 2.7272727272727275
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 57000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 248000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            222,
            960,
            116,
            0.23
        ],
        "answer": 0.23
    },
    {
        "question": "Patterson wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 36cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            5,
            38,
            26,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            27,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Meyer began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 679,
        "options": [
            679,
            0,
            680,
            681
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 38 ohms and 48 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            38,
            86,
            6,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 13 ohms and 45 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            13,
            45,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 89 grapes , how many grapes can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 148,
        "options": [
            89,
            148,
            237,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 74000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 968000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            0.076,
            598,
            533,
            51
        ],
        "answer": 0.076
    },
    {
        "question": "Olson began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            5,
            0,
            4,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            2,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            7,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Nguyen wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 18cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            15,
            18,
            28,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 50 fan, 58 sofa, 4 cat, and 3 dog? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            62,
            120,
            62,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            4,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shaurya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 147,
        "options": [
            149,
            148,
            0,
            147
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 sofa, 84 couch, 55 pair of shoes, 11 fungi spots, and 12 human beings? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 146,
        "options": [
            146,
            91,
            66,
            147
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            4,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            0,
            9,
            8,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hicks began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            18,
            0,
            16,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 2 cake , how many cake can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            2,
            9,
            11,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 bed, 33 cycles, 47 table, 12 snail, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            59,
            25,
            24,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 123 grapes , how many grapes can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            123,
            65,
            188,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 50 miles in 1 hours and 39 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.8080808080808081,
            4.901137276573305,
            3.015029455831539,
            8.20842237756559
        ],
        "answer": 0.8080808080808081
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 37 miles in 2 hours and 1 minutes?",
        "options": [
            4.590504294159251,
            5.770187580596975,
            8.66518420675381,
            18.34710743801653
        ],
        "answer": 18.34710743801653
    },
    {
        "question": "Herrera began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            105,
            107,
            0,
            106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 flower vase, 95 pair of shoes, 31 sofa, 11 dog, and 6 snail? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 129,
        "options": [
            130,
            129,
            98,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 89000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 33000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            191,
            2696969.697,
            846,
            698
        ],
        "answer": 2696969.697
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 tubelight, 25 broom, 92 flower vase, 3 crows, and 2 fungi spots? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 124,
        "options": [
            124,
            32,
            95,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 48 ohms and 48 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            48,
            10,
            48,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 bed, 43 broom, 43 refrigerator, 10 algae spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            6,
            89,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 8 cake , how many cake can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            8,
            10,
            18,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 22000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 483000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            491,
            881,
            45548.654,
            787
        ],
        "answer": 45548.654
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 refrigerator, 22 fan, 97 cycles, 3 algae spots, and 13 snail? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            70,
            7,
            117,
            124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 61 miles in 6 hours and 24 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.738260992158596,
            3.2675092675998005,
            9.53125,
            2.0507889859262614
        ],
        "answer": 9.53125
    },
    {
        "question": "Shaw wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 36cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            2,
            41,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 30 ohms and 10 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            30,
            10,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 pair of shoes, 19 bed, 60 tubelight, 5 cockroaches, and 15 cat? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 91,
        "options": [
            91,
            65,
            92,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 flower vase, 43 sofa, 86 mat, 9 fungi spots, and 3 dog? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            66,
            11,
            59,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 10 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            10,
            28,
            38,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 refrigerator, 5 bed, 45 couch, 8 pigeons, and 7 dog? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            66,
            53,
            20,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 11 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            12,
            10,
            9,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of West increased from 753 per month to 873 per month while the salary of Cook increased from 400 to 712 and of Jones increased from 454 to 761 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Jones",
        "options": [
            "West",
            "Cook",
            "Jones",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 33 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            14,
            11.0,
            63,
            34
        ],
        "answer": 11.0
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            2,
            -27,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 tubelight, 89 empty boxes, 24 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 7 plants? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            124,
            11,
            104
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 17cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            21,
            38,
            20,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 19 apples , how many apples can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            19,
            16,
            35,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Peterson wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 9.624 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 2.45,
        "options": [
            2.45,
            24.5,
            2.5500000000000003,
            9.624
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 12 bed, 39 cycles, 13 crows, and 6 cat? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            19,
            52,
            19,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 21 ohms and 46 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            46,
            67,
            21,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcdonald wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 3.318 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 1.28,
        "options": [
            1.3800000000000001,
            3.318,
            12.8,
            1.28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 sofa, 84 couch, 55 pair of shoes, 11 fungi spots, and 12 human beings? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 146,
        "options": [
            66,
            91,
            147,
            146
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 33 ohms and 44 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            1452,
            7,
            0,
            77,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 10 cake , how many cake can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            10,
            1,
            11,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 18 miles in 4 hours and 13 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.557886794395627,
            7.854427211803744,
            4.2687747035573125,
            8.360181185146839
        ],
        "answer": 4.2687747035573125
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 41 ohms and 21 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            0,
            9,
            7,
            861,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 25.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            135,
            500,
            434,
            80.5
        ],
        "answer": 80.5
    },
    {
        "question": "Butler wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 11cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            3,
            5,
            23,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 couch, 63 tubelight, 44 empty boxes, 14 dog, and 15 people? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            58,
            120,
            121,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bennett began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 235,
        "options": [
            237,
            236,
            0,
            235
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 flower vase, 95 pair of shoes, 31 sofa, 11 dog, and 6 snail? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            28,
            107,
            119,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 27.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            271,
            115.2,
            170,
            124
        ],
        "answer": 115.2
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            8,
            26,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 35 ohms and 30 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 17 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            30,
            65,
            1050,
            17,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            2550,
            2099,
            1217,
            4032
        ],
        "answer": 4032
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 19 lemons , how many lemons can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            19,
            17,
            36,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 34 empty boxes, 17 table, 4 algae spots, and 5 cockroaches? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            25,
            315,
            180,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Krishna began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 203,
        "options": [
            203,
            205,
            204,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 48 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            34,
            864,
            6,
            66,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dixon wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 5cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            20,
            23,
            27,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nichols began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            29,
            27,
            0,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $36 to the charity and a total of $14748 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            409,
            399,
            305,
            866
        ],
        "answer": 409
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 52000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 797000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            928,
            182,
            274,
            65244.668
        ],
        "answer": 65244.668
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 67 pair of shoes, 94 bed, 9 cockroaches, and 13 crows? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            149,
            173,
            121,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Young wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 40cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            45,
            31,
            15,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 flower vase, 52 mat, 10 couch, 1 cockroaches, and 3 human beings? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            69,
            68,
            3,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 10 men, 6 women, 5 children of less than 10 years, 9 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            117,
            30,
            0,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            27,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Taylor wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 3.511 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 1.26,
        "options": [
            3.511,
            12.6,
            1.26,
            1.36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            8,
            26,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 40 cycles, 8 fan, 7 human beings, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            69,
            35,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 mat, 63 chair, 28 fan, 12 trees, and 1 cat? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            42,
            90,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Taylor began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 534,
        "options": [
            0,
            535,
            534,
            536
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Woods wants to put a house in a street.The street is 8.923 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 3.33,
        "options": [
            3.33,
            8.923,
            3.43,
            33.3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of West increased from 603 per month to 664 per month while the salary of Young increased from 307 to 454 and of Robinson increased from 844 to 900 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Robinson",
        "options": [
            "West",
            "Young",
            "Robinson",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 12.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            298,
            52.4,
            480,
            154
        ],
        "answer": 52.4
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 9 ohms and 12 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            21,
            12,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ishaan wants to put a house in a street.The street is 7.864 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 6.77,
        "options": [
            67.69999999999999,
            6.77,
            7.864,
            6.869999999999999
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 9 apples , how many apples can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            9,
            27,
            36,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hart wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 16cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            34,
            25,
            37,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1453.In his greatest win, he looted 614459398 of 2881860457 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1658,
            1780,
            1436,
            1545
        ],
        "answer": 1436
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 20 ohms and 10 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            200,
            7,
            6,
            0,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            0,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 broom, 33 refrigerator, 41 pair of shoes, 8 cat, and 11 human beings? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            60,
            80,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mohammed began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 148,
        "options": [
            148,
            0,
            150,
            149
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 2 feet by 9 feet?",
        "options": [
            5609,
            9839,
            2592,
            3913
        ],
        "answer": 2592
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            5,
            -16,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "Tucker wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 6.061 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 4.55,
        "options": [
            4.6499999999999995,
            4.55,
            45.5,
            6.061
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gonzalez earns $18 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Gonzalez was paid $4863, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            452,
            271,
            261,
            77
        ],
        "answer": 261
    },
    {
        "question": "Alvarez wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 5.163 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 1.1,
        "options": [
            11.0,
            1.2000000000000002,
            5.163,
            1.1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 3 sofa, 13 pair of shoes, 5 cat, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            16,
            30,
            29,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnav began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 679,
        "options": [
            680,
            679,
            681,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 85 miles in 8 hours and 51 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.361487199593843,
            6.074278202400209,
            0.256120527306968,
            3.559620141794806
        ],
        "answer": 0.256120527306968
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 78000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 847000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            92.09,
            212,
            35,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 92.09
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $28 to the charity and a total of $19036 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            248,
            928,
            679,
            263
        ],
        "answer": 679
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            4,
            1,
            8,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -28,
            28,
            22,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Baker wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 6.618 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 2.94,
        "options": [
            3.04,
            2.94,
            6.618,
            29.4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 29 miles in 10 hours and 22 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.4683687683673146,
            4.347849183159081,
            2.797427652733119,
            4.570793476106089
        ],
        "answer": 2.797427652733119
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 55. When the sun is at 114 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            54,
            59,
            64,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 22 watermelon , how many watermelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            22,
            16,
            38,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            6,
            5,
            0,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Washington wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 22cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            6,
            27,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 50 fan, 58 sofa, 4 cat, and 3 dog? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            7,
            8,
            62,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 32.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            133.0,
            474,
            225,
            291
        ],
        "answer": 133.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 3.734 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 1.68,
        "options": [
            1.68,
            1.78,
            16.8,
            3.734
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bennett wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 16cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            22,
            21,
            20,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 broom, 33 refrigerator, 41 pair of shoes, 8 cat, and 11 human beings? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            72,
            62,
            9,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cruz wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 3.729 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 1.68,
        "options": [
            16.8,
            1.68,
            1.78,
            3.729
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 16.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            303,
            440,
            473,
            97.6
        ],
        "answer": 97.6
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            5,
            -16,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 14 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            4,
            -11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 18.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            142,
            332,
            347,
            56.4
        ],
        "answer": 56.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Dixon began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 500,
        "options": [
            502,
            501,
            0,
            500
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 15 watermelon , how many watermelon can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            15,
            28,
            43,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 198 grapes , how many grapes can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 97,
        "options": [
            198,
            97,
            295,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 83 miles in 9 hours and 16 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.7227566861816141,
            9.756162650304022,
            6.987998085211721,
            0.23884892086330936
        ],
        "answer": 0.23884892086330936
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 46 miles in 1 hours and 14 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.942161690107104,
            7.139321645702116,
            4.15766270173021,
            59.675675675675684
        ],
        "answer": 59.675675675675684
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 80 miles in 3 hours and 38 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.035006212465733,
            6.654711490020123,
            6.81347321128754,
            22.018348623853214
        ],
        "answer": 22.018348623853214
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 46 ohms and 11 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            6,
            57,
            506,
            12,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 6 feet by 5 feet?",
        "options": [
            4320,
            8250,
            8027,
            3624
        ],
        "answer": 4320
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            10,
            -25,
            15,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 30.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            276.2,
            340,
            383,
            434
        ],
        "answer": 276.2
    },
    {
        "question": "Mendoza wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 21cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            21,
            30,
            5,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 50 fan, 58 sofa, 4 cat, and 3 dog? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            93,
            115,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Holmes wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 13cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            14,
            9,
            22,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 56. When the sun is at 29 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            78,
            21,
            47,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 sofa, 61 table, 63 bed, 8 snail, and 10 fungi spots? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 127,
        "options": [
            187,
            0,
            293,
            127
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 88 pair of shoes, 94 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 5 plants? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 127,
        "options": [
            351,
            127,
            297,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            15,
            5,
            8,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -28,
            28,
            22,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 pair of shoes, 19 bed, 60 tubelight, 5 cockroaches, and 15 cat? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            76,
            4,
            75,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 24.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            191.8,
            361,
            437,
            203
        ],
        "answer": 191.8
    },
    {
        "question": "Diya wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 36cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            2,
            35,
            2,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            7,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 empty boxes, 73 flower vase, 53 mat, 10 fungi spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            63,
            22,
            78,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 37 tubelight, 38 cycles, 12 crows, and 10 snail? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            0,
            38,
            280,
            310
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 1 feet by 4 feet?",
        "options": [
            576,
            6476,
            9855,
            9246
        ],
        "answer": 576
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 84 grapes , how many grapes can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 121,
        "options": [
            84,
            121,
            205,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 9 sofa, 93 couch, 11 people, and 7 cockroaches? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            119,
            106,
            75,
            116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -19,
            18,
            19,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 78. When the sun is at 105 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            110,
            97,
            99,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Webb increased from 400 per month to 584 per month while the salary of Darsh increased from 406 to 887 and of Veer increased from 651 to 665 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Veer",
        "options": [
            "Webb",
            "Darsh",
            "Veer",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 13 ohms and 25 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 17 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            38,
            17,
            25,
            46,
            325
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 4 men, 4 women, 9 children of less than 10 years, 10 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            107,
            27,
            0,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 24 chocolates , how many chocolates can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            24,
            25,
            49,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hamilton wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 8.818 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 6.29,
        "options": [
            6.29,
            6.39,
            62.9,
            8.818
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 67. When the sun is at 174 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            30,
            74,
            56,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 28 miles in 2 hours and 20 minutes?",
        "options": [
            4.176876709471076,
            8.368984708729222,
            9.275767249708414,
            0.2
        ],
        "answer": 0.2
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 5 cake , how many cake can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            5,
            6,
            11,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $54 to the charity and a total of $11049 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            38,
            492,
            204,
            368
        ],
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 12 bed, 39 cycles, 13 crows, and 6 cat? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            32,
            77,
            72,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            30,
            13,
            17,
            -30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 16 ohms and 43 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            16,
            7,
            43,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 85 miles in 8 hours and 56 minutes?",
        "options": [
            3.0602039146405744,
            5.304199014800092,
            4.209558192753581,
            0.15858208955223882
        ],
        "answer": 0.15858208955223882
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 41 ohms and 21 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            21,
            8,
            41,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 43 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 11 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            70,
            11,
            40,
            1161,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 chair, 7 tubelight, 2 bed, 9 algae spots, and 12 dog? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            12,
            14,
            11,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Palmer earns $19 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $3 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Palmer was paid $2258, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            304,
            381,
            220,
            116
        ],
        "answer": 116
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 21 apples , how many apples can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            21,
            24,
            45,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 49.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            495,
            440.0,
            459,
            440
        ],
        "answer": 440.0
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            2,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            9,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gutierrez wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 6.335 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 2.61,
        "options": [
            26.099999999999998,
            2.61,
            2.71,
            6.335
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 24 tubelight, 86 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 11 crows? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 123,
        "options": [
            123,
            124,
            37,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 chair, 39 couch, 5 bed, 13 people, and 11 algae spots? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            55,
            18,
            56,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 cycles, 75 bed, 7 sofa, 2 snail, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            27,
            32,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -28,
            28,
            22,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 19 ohms and 36 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            19,
            36,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 20 lemons , how many lemons can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            20,
            17,
            37,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 23000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 521000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            39,
            44145.873,
            828,
            645
        ],
        "answer": 44145.873
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 13 ohms and 25 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            38,
            13,
            4,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alvarez wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 20cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            11,
            12,
            6,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 bed, 57 table, 12 fan, 13 fungi spots, and 9 people? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            0,
            255,
            230
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 7.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            87,
            36.0,
            105,
            99
        ],
        "answer": 36.0
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 tubelight, 43 couch, 65 table, 4 people, and 9 plants? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            118,
            107,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Stone increased from 740 per month to 971 per month while the salary of Price increased from 322 to 794 and of Pari increased from 952 to 994 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Pari",
        "options": [
            "Stone",
            "Price",
            "Pari",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lewis wants to put a house in a street.The street is 8.117 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 1.61,
        "options": [
            16.1,
            8.117,
            1.61,
            1.7100000000000002
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 8years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "Saturday",
            "Monday",
            "tuesday",
            "Friday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -11,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "Anaya wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 18cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            10,
            14,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Robertson wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 8.306 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 1.44,
        "options": [
            1.44,
            14.399999999999999,
            8.306,
            1.54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aadhya wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 19cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            15,
            17,
            12,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 10 men, 9 women, 2 children of less than 10 years, 5 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            108,
            26,
            0,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            30,
            13,
            17,
            -30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            0,
            5,
            4,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 flower vase, 33 table, 84 cycles, 15 pigeons, and 8 human beings? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 132,
        "options": [
            133,
            48,
            132,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 163 grapes , how many grapes can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            163,
            73,
            236,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ramirez wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 37cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            12,
            28,
            31,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 22 miles in 10 hours and 25 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.3373662793726275,
            3.764042841651534,
            0.05632,
            6.551072956475702
        ],
        "answer": 0.05632
    },
    {
        "question": "Nelson began counting from 0. She skip-counted by nine's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 783,
        "options": [
            0,
            785,
            783,
            784
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 cycles, 75 bed, 7 sofa, 2 snail, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            16,
            9,
            76,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            16,
            8,
            9,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 62. When the sun is at 43 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            73,
            45,
            19,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 34.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            141,
            437,
            136,
            136.8
        ],
        "answer": 136.8
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 24.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            151,
            51.6,
            317,
            281
        ],
        "answer": 51.6
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            10,
            -25,
            15,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            -27,
            22,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 48 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            8,
            18,
            66,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 34 empty boxes, 17 table, 4 algae spots, and 5 cockroaches? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            10,
            21,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 chair, 26 pair of shoes, 88 cycles, 15 cockroaches, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            32,
            103,
            22,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 26. When the sun is at 98 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            85,
            36,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 34 empty boxes, 17 table, 4 algae spots, and 5 cockroaches? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            66,
            60,
            68,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 87 miles in 10 hours and 35 minutes?",
        "options": [
            3.23459625469351,
            9.491972348639122,
            0.13700787401574804,
            3.477135242629142
        ],
        "answer": 0.13700787401574804
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 35 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            35,
            79,
            7,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            14,
            11,
            25,
            -25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            -25,
            25,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 empty boxes, 73 flower vase, 53 mat, 10 fungi spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            105,
            18,
            78,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 47.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            188.6,
            414,
            191,
            405
        ],
        "answer": 188.6
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 25 chocolates , how many chocolates can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            53,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            25,
            -25,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 45.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            369,
            394,
            436,
            358.8
        ],
        "answer": 358.8
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 50 ohms and 47 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            97,
            47,
            2,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 27 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/10 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            46,
            55,
            93,
            8.1
        ],
        "answer": 8.1
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            14,
            5,
            4,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 48 ohms and 48 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            2304,
            96,
            9,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 25 chocolates , how many chocolates can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            25,
            29,
            54,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Harris wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 37cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            35,
            7,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            1,
            3,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 20 ohms and 10 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            30,
            20,
            3,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 58 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 5/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            32.22,
            16,
            28,
            47
        ],
        "answer": 32.22
    },
    {
        "question": "Burns wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 33cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            27,
            42,
            35,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 14 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            4,
            -11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Monday and returns to the bank 6years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Sunday",
        "options": [
            "Saturday",
            "Thursday",
            "Saturday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 bed, 43 broom, 43 refrigerator, 10 algae spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            58,
            108,
            9,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 12.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            92,
            72.0,
            281,
            456
        ],
        "answer": 72.0
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 34 empty boxes, 17 table, 4 algae spots, and 5 cockroaches? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            21,
            60,
            42,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 20 chocolates , how many chocolates can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            20,
            18,
            38,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 50 miles in 3 hours and 12 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.468242788398912,
            15.625000000000002,
            7.617320215727226,
            8.509788153103385
        ],
        "answer": 15.625000000000002
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            2,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 26 ohms and 15 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            7,
            15,
            41,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 24 tubelight, 86 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 11 crows? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 123,
        "options": [
            123,
            37,
            124,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            20,
            -23,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Clark wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 6.884 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 2.42,
        "options": [
            6.884,
            2.52,
            2.42,
            24.2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 30. When the sun is at 70 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            59,
            55,
            61,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 44 miles in 7 hours and 45 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.083870967741936,
            9.866392281837763,
            4.499939918923685,
            5.7366972015120865
        ],
        "answer": 9.083870967741936
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 16.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            133.6,
            198,
            499,
            474
        ],
        "answer": 133.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Kennedy wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 6.956 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 5.49,
        "options": [
            54.900000000000006,
            6.956,
            5.49,
            5.59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Young wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 4.102 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 1.05,
        "options": [
            10.5,
            1.1500000000000001,
            1.05,
            4.102
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $68 to the charity and a total of $13468 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            241,
            198,
            255,
            451
        ],
        "answer": 198
    },
    {
        "question": "Navya wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 4.93 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 2.52,
        "options": [
            25.2,
            2.52,
            4.93,
            2.62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            5,
            12,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wilson wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 14cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            13,
            18,
            2,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Garcia wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 38cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            39,
            22,
            9,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            5,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            5,
            -25,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 17 ohms and 7 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            7,
            10,
            17,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 35 ohms and 21 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            56,
            21,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 36. When the sun is at 172 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 82,
        "options": [
            10,
            82,
            9,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wright began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            74,
            0,
            76,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 34 empty boxes, 17 table, 4 algae spots, and 5 cockroaches? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            21,
            60,
            59,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 1 feet by 10 feet?",
        "options": [
            5028,
            1440,
            2239,
            6570
        ],
        "answer": 1440
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 27 miles in 5 hours and 14 minutes?",
        "options": [
            4.514455010883707,
            8.019631680937845,
            6.778793341076236,
            0.08598726114649681
        ],
        "answer": 0.08598726114649681
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            0,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 199 grapes , how many grapes can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            199,
            85,
            284,
            114
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 15 watermelon , how many watermelon can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            15,
            25,
            40,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            0,
            20,
            10,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 45 miles in 3 hours and 43 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.616124718860031,
            8.849552145261846,
            19.37219730941704,
            1.5690692684926384
        ],
        "answer": 19.37219730941704
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 13 ohms and 45 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            45,
            585,
            58,
            34,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 8 watermelon , how many watermelon can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            8,
            6,
            14,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 29 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            29,
            25,
            54,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            7,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            0,
            11,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anaya wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 9cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            6,
            45,
            9,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 88 pair of shoes, 94 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 5 plants? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            92,
            109,
            4,
            164
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ahana wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 31cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            41,
            17,
            9,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Peterson increased from 565 per month to 642 per month while the salary of Elliott increased from 456 to 738 and of Gibson increased from 753 to 873 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Gibson",
        "options": [
            "Peterson",
            "Elliott",
            "Gibson",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            5,
            -16,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 26000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 837000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            955,
            905,
            31063.321,
            965
        ],
        "answer": 31063.321
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 28 apples , how many apples can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            28,
            23,
            51,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Boyd wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 40cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            9,
            44,
            17,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            14,
            11,
            25,
            -25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            19,
            7,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1399.In his greatest win, he looted 317363778 of 4977523597 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1387,
            1569,
            1543,
            1487
        ],
        "answer": 1387
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 27 watermelon , how many watermelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            27,
            11,
            38,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 29 watermelon , how many watermelon can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            29,
            25,
            54,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 10 watermelon , how many watermelon can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            10,
            22,
            32,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 27 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            27,
            10,
            27,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $72 to the charity and a total of $13904 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            905,
            193,
            670,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 9 apples , how many apples can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            9,
            21,
            30,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 sofa, 61 table, 63 bed, 8 snail, and 10 fungi spots? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 125,
        "options": [
            62,
            126,
            71,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 sofa, 61 table, 63 bed, 8 snail, and 10 fungi spots? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            74,
            25,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            -1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 13 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            28,
            25,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 88 pair of shoes, 94 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 5 plants? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 184,
        "options": [
            184,
            96,
            185,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            0,
            4,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 9 ohms and 12 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            9,
            21,
            8,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            4,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            11,
            1,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bell wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 5.202 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 3.81,
        "options": [
            3.91,
            38.1,
            3.81,
            5.202
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            0,
            5,
            17,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 77 miles in 1 hours and 32 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.794627924894111,
            1.3391304347826087,
            8.877404525380015,
            9.889627254034894
        ],
        "answer": 1.3391304347826087
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 7 cake , how many cake can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            7,
            2,
            9,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 67 pair of shoes, 94 bed, 9 cockroaches, and 13 crows? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 165,
        "options": [
            103,
            165,
            71,
            166
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 8.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            394,
            445,
            65,
            58.6
        ],
        "answer": 58.6
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 33 ohms and 44 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            44,
            33,
            77,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 6 feet by 3 feet?",
        "options": [
            7507,
            2592,
            4930,
            5265
        ],
        "answer": 2592
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 35 ohms and 21 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 22 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            735,
            22,
            21,
            50,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 19 lemons , how many lemons can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            19,
            30,
            49,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 67 pair of shoes, 94 bed, 9 cockroaches, and 13 crows? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            129,
            56,
            154
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 20 ohms and 10 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 23 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            10,
            23,
            200,
            53,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            7,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Snyder wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 7.294 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 5.19,
        "options": [
            7.294,
            51.900000000000006,
            5.19,
            5.29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 22 chocolates , how many chocolates can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            22,
            25,
            47,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            8,
            2,
            10,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kabir earns $20 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $3 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Kabir was paid $2558, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            277,
            124,
            53,
            267
        ],
        "answer": 124
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 24 tubelight, 86 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 11 crows? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 108,
        "options": [
            125,
            132,
            108,
            128
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 40 cycles, 8 fan, 7 human beings, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            15,
            49,
            20,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 24 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            24,
            2,
            19,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mendoza wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 5.191 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 3.49,
        "options": [
            3.5900000000000003,
            34.900000000000006,
            5.191,
            3.49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Moreno wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 3.729 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 1.58,
        "options": [
            15.8,
            1.58,
            1.6800000000000002,
            3.729
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 147,
        "options": [
            149,
            147,
            0,
            148
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 26 ohms and 5 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            130,
            5,
            31,
            0,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 70 miles in 2 hours and 44 minutes?",
        "options": [
            4.789074891434376,
            4.715176273727744,
            0.6829268292682927,
            1.5616060635168236
        ],
        "answer": 0.6829268292682927
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 flower vase, 90 pair of shoes, 18 refrigerator, 3 cockroaches, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            100,
            18,
            19,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Griffin wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 39cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            37,
            39,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            6,
            14,
            7,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 33 ohms and 9 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 20 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            42,
            20,
            297,
            50,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $32 to the charity and a total of $10224 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            240,
            319,
            217,
            951
        ],
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 chair, 26 pair of shoes, 88 cycles, 15 cockroaches, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            5,
            129,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Herrera wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 4.143 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 2.48,
        "options": [
            2.58,
            24.8,
            4.143,
            2.48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 71. When the sun is at 89 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            74,
            106,
            100,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arjun wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 6cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            14,
            37,
            21,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hansen wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 37cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            28,
            12,
            43,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nichols wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 9cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            6,
            9,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $52 to the charity and a total of $8308 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            29,
            152,
            159,
            906
        ],
        "answer": 159
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 30 lemons , how many lemons can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            30,
            18,
            48,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 cycles, 77 empty boxes, 12 bed, 4 human beings, and 11 cat? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            82,
            16,
            16,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 table, 58 empty boxes, 12 flower vase, 5 fungi spots, and 1 trees? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            71,
            6,
            7,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 24.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            445,
            217.7,
            299,
            253
        ],
        "answer": 217.7
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Moreno began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 301,
        "options": [
            303,
            0,
            301,
            302
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            4,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 pair of shoes, 67 chair, 8 bed, 12 plants, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            20,
            13,
            14,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stevens wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 3.901 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 2.29,
        "options": [
            2.29,
            3.901,
            2.39,
            22.9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            -25,
            25,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            1,
            4,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Veer wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 19cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            14,
            18,
            15,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 19.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            151,
            113,
            64.1,
            485
        ],
        "answer": 64.1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ross wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 9cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            15,
            16,
            6,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            25,
            -25,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            30,
            13,
            17,
            -30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 27 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            54,
            8,
            27,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 19.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            428,
            384,
            116.0,
            348
        ],
        "answer": 116.0
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 28 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            44,
            28,
            3,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 mat, 40 couch, 77 cycles, 4 plants, and 14 cat? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            130,
            52,
            123,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 112 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 5/7 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            50,
            64,
            34,
            80.0
        ],
        "answer": 80.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 13 years old in the year 1491.In his greatest win, he looted 735739309 of 8296345930 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1693,
            1588,
            1478,
            1814
        ],
        "answer": 1478
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 4 cake , how many cake can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            4,
            6,
            10,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            10,
            -25,
            15,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 13 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            28,
            25,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 11.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            132,
            455,
            392,
            27.6
        ],
        "answer": 27.6
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            8,
            26,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 36.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            179,
            253,
            415,
            145.8
        ],
        "answer": 145.8
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 broom, 20 pair of shoes, 43 sofa, 11 cat, and 13 crows? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            76,
            54,
            33,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 table, 58 empty boxes, 12 flower vase, 5 fungi spots, and 1 trees? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            83,
            84,
            17,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            10,
            -25,
            15,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 bed, 57 table, 12 fan, 13 fungi spots, and 9 people? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            73,
            90,
            98,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Harris wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 10cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            14,
            18,
            15,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            5,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $64 to the charity and a total of $19960 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            234,
            311,
            249,
            243
        ],
        "answer": 311
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            30,
            13,
            17,
            -30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            0,
            5,
            12,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 6000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 453000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            367,
            0.013,
            530,
            842
        ],
        "answer": 0.013
    },
    {
        "question": "James wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 37cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            6,
            37,
            13,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 164 grapes , how many grapes can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            164,
            74,
            238,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Smith wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 13cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            34,
            28,
            27,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $20 to the charity and a total of $9842 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            716,
            492,
            704,
            558
        ],
        "answer": 492
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 flower vase, 95 pair of shoes, 31 sofa, 11 dog, and 6 snail? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            17,
            18,
            42,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 40 ohms and 42 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            42,
            4,
            82,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            10,
            -25,
            15,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 18 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            24,
            12,
            -24
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 35 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            44,
            35,
            8,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 couch, 63 tubelight, 44 empty boxes, 14 dog, and 15 people? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 142,
        "options": [
            142,
            0,
            247,
            393
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            9,
            0,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            20,
            -23,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 97 miles in 8 hours and 31 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.796407557918238,
            2.164901182485643,
            2.036922837747797,
            18.22309197651664
        ],
        "answer": 18.22309197651664
    },
    {
        "question": "Green wants to put a car in a road.The road is 3.44 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 1.38,
        "options": [
            1.48,
            3.44,
            13.799999999999999,
            1.38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            7,
            8,
            20,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            5,
            -16,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 38 ohms and 48 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            86,
            38,
            48,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 3 cake , how many cake can a man eat?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            3,
            2,
            5,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 8 ohms and 12 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 1 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            20,
            1,
            8,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Foster wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 9.98 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 5.06,
        "options": [
            50.599999999999994,
            5.06,
            5.159999999999999,
            9.98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 tubelight, 25 broom, 92 flower vase, 3 crows, and 2 fungi spots? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            51,
            53,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $98 to the charity and a total of $8842 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            248,
            153,
            429,
            90
        ],
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 5 ohms and 20 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            4,
            0,
            1,
            25,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            12,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 50 fan, 58 sofa, 4 cat, and 3 dog? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            62,
            62,
            121,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 broom, 23 fan, 5 couch, 10 algae spots, and 5 trees? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            0,
            18,
            394,
            334
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 35 ohms and 30 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            30,
            65,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 flower vase, 95 pair of shoes, 31 sofa, 11 dog, and 6 snail? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 129,
        "options": [
            130,
            42,
            98,
            129
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            4,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Prisha wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 27cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            33,
            13,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 20 lemons , how many lemons can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            20,
            21,
            41,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 mat, 40 couch, 77 cycles, 4 plants, and 14 cat? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            18,
            41,
            19,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 47.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            402,
            451,
            377.2,
            429
        ],
        "answer": 377.2
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 24 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            19,
            24,
            10,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 8.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            198,
            62.0,
            437,
            374
        ],
        "answer": 62.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Rodriguez wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 31cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            17,
            38,
            22,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            8,
            2,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 28 chocolates , how many chocolates can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            28,
            17,
            45,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 59 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 1/8 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            100,
            7.38,
            44,
            69
        ],
        "answer": 7.38
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 40 ohms and 31 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 1 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            71,
            40,
            31,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            26,
            0,
            24,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 34 miles in 5 hours and 11 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.17491961414791,
            2.2845415663600654,
            9.765513494996933,
            9.069239693635417
        ],
        "answer": 0.17491961414791
    },
    {
        "question": "Ananya wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 12cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            22,
            23,
            21,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 26.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            96,
            359,
            84.9,
            200
        ],
        "answer": 84.9
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            3,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 flower vase, 95 pair of shoes, 31 sofa, 11 dog, and 6 snail? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 139,
        "options": [
            313,
            268,
            139,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 33.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            100.8,
            261,
            297,
            224
        ],
        "answer": 100.8
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 8 feet?",
        "options": [
            4608,
            6472,
            3876,
            4068
        ],
        "answer": 4608
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 mat, 40 couch, 77 cycles, 4 plants, and 14 cat? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            81,
            41,
            19,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 72 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 4/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            95,
            54,
            49,
            32.0
        ],
        "answer": 32.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $64 to the charity and a total of $8595 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            392,
            314,
            134,
            191
        ],
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 19 ohms and 32 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            51,
            3,
            32,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hill wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 7cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            12,
            10,
            14,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 69 broom, 92 mat, 1 cockroaches, and 8 cat? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            10,
            93,
            9,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            20,
            -23,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Clark wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 8.503 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 6.16,
        "options": [
            6.16,
            6.26,
            61.6,
            8.503
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            20,
            -23,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 25 grapes , how many grapes can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            25,
            65,
            90,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 13 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            28,
            25,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 98 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/10 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            86,
            94,
            29.4,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 29.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Anaya wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 7.348 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 2.29,
        "options": [
            2.29,
            22.9,
            7.348,
            2.39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wagner began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            60,
            62,
            0,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 19 ohms and 32 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 20 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            20,
            608,
            51,
            32,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -11,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 sofa, 84 couch, 55 pair of shoes, 11 fungi spots, and 12 human beings? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 131,
        "options": [
            0,
            131,
            312,
            243
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Freeman wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 22cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            42,
            42,
            20,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            8,
            26,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 7 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            7,
            14,
            21,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            7,
            10,
            9,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 82 miles in 10 hours and 28 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.062651961607115,
            5.468462193477545,
            9.940017465639556,
            0.1305732484076433
        ],
        "answer": 0.1305732484076433
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Henderson increased from 939 per month to 975 per month while the salary of Ruiz increased from 433 to 807 and of Webb increased from 810 to 967 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Webb",
        "options": [
            "Henderson",
            "Ruiz",
            "Webb",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stone wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 4.177 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 2.27,
        "options": [
            4.177,
            2.37,
            22.7,
            2.27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Taylor wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 11cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            13,
            34,
            36,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 broom, 23 fan, 5 couch, 10 algae spots, and 5 trees? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            16,
            15,
            34,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 empty boxes, 73 flower vase, 53 mat, 10 fungi spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 131,
        "options": [
            63,
            78,
            131,
            132
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 empty boxes, 60 cycles, 58 refrigerator, 1 pigeons, and 11 trees? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            14,
            20,
            113
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 couch, 63 tubelight, 44 empty boxes, 14 dog, and 15 people? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            58,
            120,
            121,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Russell wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 21cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            11,
            7,
            10,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 6.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            62,
            213,
            60.3,
            79
        ],
        "answer": 60.3
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 flower vase, 43 sofa, 86 mat, 9 fungi spots, and 3 dog? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            13,
            44,
            95,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            10,
            19,
            11,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 3000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 636000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            820,
            404,
            189,
            0.005
        ],
        "answer": 0.005
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 7 cake , how many cake can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            7,
            10,
            17,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 24 watermelon , how many watermelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            24,
            29,
            53,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $30 to the charity and a total of $5998 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            288,
            159,
            199,
            278
        ],
        "answer": 199
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -11,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 75 miles in 1 hours and 24 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.688110450729564,
            0.8928571428571429,
            3.851143065287574,
            4.087319674280255
        ],
        "answer": 0.8928571428571429
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 40 cycles, 8 fan, 7 human beings, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            58,
            15,
            57,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            13,
            11,
            20,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Roberts wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 9cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            16,
            3,
            37,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mason wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 25cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            26,
            10,
            9,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            2,
            -27,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Ananya wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 20cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            16,
            20,
            26,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 121 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 1/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            75,
            13,
            39,
            13.44
        ],
        "answer": 13.44
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 24 apples , how many apples can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            24,
            25,
            49,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            5,
            -16,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 47 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 5/6 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            75,
            96,
            39.17,
            53
        ],
        "answer": 39.17
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 48.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            446,
            195.8,
            310,
            257
        ],
        "answer": 195.8
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            11,
            4,
            4,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 21 ohms and 46 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            10,
            0,
            67,
            966,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 18 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            24,
            12,
            -24
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            -25,
            25,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 sofa, 61 table, 63 bed, 8 snail, and 10 fungi spots? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 115,
        "options": [
            129,
            135,
            115,
            140
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Martinez began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 208,
        "options": [
            208,
            210,
            0,
            209
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 30 flower vase, 24 sofa, 2 plants, and 2 dog? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            43,
            67,
            26,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Moreno began counting from 0. She skip-counted by nine's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            73,
            0,
            72,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            4,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $34 to the charity and a total of $8692 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            797,
            467,
            877,
            255
        ],
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 22 apples , how many apples can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            22,
            13,
            35,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Taylor began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 250,
        "options": [
            250,
            251,
            0,
            252
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 mat, 40 couch, 77 cycles, 4 plants, and 14 cat? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            57,
            18,
            113,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kian wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 34cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            30,
            39,
            28,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reed began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 144,
        "options": [
            144,
            145,
            146,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 50 ohms and 20 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            50,
            70,
            4,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            0,
            12,
            6,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fernandez began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 172,
        "options": [
            173,
            172,
            0,
            174
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vasquez wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 6.136 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 3.21,
        "options": [
            3.31,
            3.21,
            32.1,
            6.136
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 10 feet by 4 feet?",
        "options": [
            5760,
            8815,
            4398,
            5162
        ],
        "answer": 5760
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 29 sofa, 61 tubelight, 4 snail, and 12 dog? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 89,
        "options": [
            0,
            154,
            272,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 51. When the sun is at 123 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            91,
            91,
            24,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -24,
            24,
            4,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "Porter wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 13cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            33,
            20,
            14,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 flower vase, 52 mat, 10 couch, 1 cockroaches, and 3 human beings? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            57,
            68,
            11,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 29 miles in 5 hours and 14 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.218166103159904,
            0.1477707006369427,
            4.668029551837644,
            6.057227578489958
        ],
        "answer": 0.1477707006369427
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 4 men, 9 women, 10 children of less than 10 years, 9 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            108,
            32,
            0,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 1 cake , how many cake can a man eat?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            1,
            3,
            4,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 24 ohms and 25 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 23 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            23,
            600,
            49,
            50,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 20 ohms and 10 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            10,
            30,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 table, 7 refrigerator, 53 bed, 2 human beings, and 15 snail? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            55,
            17,
            18,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 36.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            233,
            233,
            146.4,
            345
        ],
        "answer": 146.4
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            3,
            8,
            4,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 81 miles in 8 hours and 25 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.25663366336633664,
            1.1832865450481682,
            3.212214886363945,
            5.3051359149771375
        ],
        "answer": 0.25663366336633664
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Warren wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 25cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            31,
            30,
            40,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 25 chair, 99 fan, 3 snail, and 5 trees? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            102,
            26,
            9,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 98 miles in 9 hours and 42 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.341455775891277,
            1.6979028435432197,
            10.103092783505156,
            8.736576051801034
        ],
        "answer": 10.103092783505156
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 86 grapes , how many grapes can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 176,
        "options": [
            86,
            176,
            262,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 tubelight, 43 couch, 65 table, 4 people, and 9 plants? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 117,
        "options": [
            52,
            118,
            117,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 21 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            6,
            11,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 refrigerator, 22 fan, 97 cycles, 3 algae spots, and 13 snail? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 122,
        "options": [
            100,
            25,
            122,
            123
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Harris began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 112,
        "options": [
            113,
            0,
            114,
            112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 pair of shoes, 67 chair, 8 bed, 12 plants, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            30,
            70,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Phillips wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 20cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            15,
            22,
            37,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 empty boxes, 83 flower vase, 50 broom, 7 trees, and 9 dog? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            17,
            98,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 29 sofa, 61 tubelight, 4 snail, and 12 dog? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            38,
            99,
            65,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 pair of shoes, 19 bed, 60 tubelight, 5 cockroaches, and 15 cat? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            105,
            93,
            93,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Eva wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 18cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            20,
            12,
            19,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 61 miles in 2 hours and 26 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.36359690902116,
            7.045407093325579,
            5.759532216516499,
            40.109589041095894
        ],
        "answer": 40.109589041095894
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 58 miles in 7 hours and 25 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.347486843785367,
            7.820224719101124,
            3.8068583127443407,
            9.081315542627626
        ],
        "answer": 7.820224719101124
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 44000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 758000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            65,
            308,
            0.058,
            495
        ],
        "answer": 0.058
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 refrigerator, 5 bed, 45 couch, 8 pigeons, and 7 dog? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            25,
            31,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $54 to the charity and a total of $7149 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            132,
            260,
            704,
            611
        ],
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "Aaradhya wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 40cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            26,
            45,
            23,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Riya earns $6 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $3 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Riya was paid $1780, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            498,
            223,
            231,
            474
        ],
        "answer": 231
    },
    {
        "question": "Sullivan wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 7.983 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 3.3,
        "options": [
            3.4,
            7.983,
            3.3,
            33.0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 108 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/8 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            40.5,
            86,
            53,
            86
        ],
        "answer": 40.5
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 29 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            29,
            22,
            51,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $62 to the charity and a total of $7384 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            732,
            119,
            932,
            85
        ],
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 flower vase, 33 table, 84 cycles, 15 pigeons, and 8 human beings? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            99,
            23,
            48,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 51 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 1/10 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            86,
            5.1,
            13,
            97
        ],
        "answer": 5.1
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            5,
            -16,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 19 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            19,
            12,
            31,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            30,
            13,
            17,
            -30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 flower vase, 90 pair of shoes, 18 refrigerator, 3 cockroaches, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            118,
            21,
            100,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anvi began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 125,
        "options": [
            125,
            127,
            0,
            126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            21,
            2,
            8,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            25,
            -25,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 13 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            28,
            25,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Olson wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 23cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            23,
            22,
            23,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 9 sofa, 93 couch, 11 people, and 7 cockroaches? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            104,
            19,
            11,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Peters wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 14cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            3,
            15,
            6,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 40 ohms and 42 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            82,
            42,
            5,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $48 to the charity and a total of $8730 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            310,
            394,
            828,
            181
        ],
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "Snyder began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 133,
        "options": [
            133,
            135,
            0,
            134
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 91000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 404000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            152,
            73,
            496,
            225247.525
        ],
        "answer": 225247.525
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            4,
            2,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Thomas wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 9.676 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 6.52,
        "options": [
            6.619999999999999,
            65.19999999999999,
            9.676,
            6.52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 12 bed, 39 cycles, 13 crows, and 6 cat? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            0,
            285,
            160,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 18 years old in the year 1159.In his greatest win, he looted 424016146 of 3214562106 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1509,
            1681,
            1658,
            1141
        ],
        "answer": 1141
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            9,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarush wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 12cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            31,
            23,
            31,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 broom, 20 pair of shoes, 43 sofa, 11 cat, and 13 crows? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            24,
            25,
            54,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 40 ohms and 31 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            8,
            40,
            31,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            14,
            11,
            25,
            -25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Aaradhya wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 26cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            33,
            19,
            23,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 43 miles in 9 hours and 49 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.0730050933786078,
            3.628036934632292,
            3.384263029118861,
            6.908710516935057
        ],
        "answer": 0.0730050933786078
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            25,
            -25,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Flores wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 27cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            42,
            33,
            23,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Saturday and returns to the bank 3years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "tuesday",
        "options": [
            "tuesday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Friday",
            "Saturday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 broom, 23 fan, 5 couch, 10 algae spots, and 5 trees? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            46,
            26,
            40,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 27 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            0,
            54,
            4,
            4,
            729
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Young began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            33,
            32,
            0,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -24,
            24,
            4,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 33000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 346000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            714,
            95.376,
            91,
            831
        ],
        "answer": 95.376
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            7,
            3,
            0,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 flower vase, 95 pair of shoes, 31 sofa, 11 dog, and 6 snail? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            99,
            106,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Miller wants to put a house in a street.The street is 5.964 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 3.59,
        "options": [
            5.964,
            3.59,
            3.69,
            35.9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 10 feet by 9 feet?",
        "options": [
            9402,
            1959,
            12960,
            3716
        ],
        "answer": 12960
    },
    {
        "question": "Fernandez wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 8cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            15,
            23,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hernandez earns $9 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $5 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Hernandez was paid $3659, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            53,
            316,
            297,
            65
        ],
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 29 sofa, 61 tubelight, 4 snail, and 12 dog? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            83,
            9,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            9,
            0,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 bed, 33 cycles, 47 table, 12 snail, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 80,
        "options": [
            93,
            105,
            80,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 49.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            470,
            356,
            378,
            292.4
        ],
        "answer": 292.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Mason began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 372,
        "options": [
            373,
            0,
            372,
            374
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 72. When the sun is at 128 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            79,
            109,
            102,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            2,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            5,
            -26,
            21,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Simmons wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 6.77 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 2.77,
        "options": [
            27.7,
            2.87,
            2.77,
            6.77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 33. When the sun is at 178 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            6,
            19,
            38,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 81. When the sun is at 170 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            47,
            14,
            83,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 32.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            477,
            277,
            128.8,
            262
        ],
        "answer": 128.8
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 24 ohms and 25 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            49,
            24,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 14 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            4,
            -11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -19,
            18,
            19,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "Gardner wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 4.7 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 1.33,
        "options": [
            1.4300000000000002,
            4.7,
            13.3,
            1.33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 10 feet by 3 feet?",
        "options": [
            3914,
            2885,
            1389,
            4320
        ],
        "answer": 4320
    },
    {
        "question": "Reed wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 30cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            34,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 67000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 745000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            26,
            80,
            0.09,
            154
        ],
        "answer": 0.09
    },
    {
        "question": "Kennedy wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 34cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            36,
            29,
            19,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 28 miles in 5 hours and 44 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.2039045898824217,
            6.5353694023187865,
            7.8139534883720945,
            9.949765245479437
        ],
        "answer": 7.8139534883720945
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 86 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 1/7 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            72,
            97,
            36,
            12.29
        ],
        "answer": 12.29
    },
    {
        "question": "Krishna wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 14cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            24,
            13,
            33,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 21 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            21,
            48,
            27,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 14 watermelon , how many watermelon can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            14,
            16,
            30,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 50 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            94,
            50,
            5,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $68 to the charity and a total of $14652 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            515,
            233,
            121,
            215
        ],
        "answer": 215
    },
    {
        "question": "Myers wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 4.174 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 2.22,
        "options": [
            4.174,
            22.200000000000003,
            2.3200000000000003,
            2.22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Chavez wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 8.148 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 2.97,
        "options": [
            3.0700000000000003,
            2.97,
            8.148,
            29.700000000000003
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 21.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            406,
            293,
            194,
            194.5
        ],
        "answer": 194.5
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            5,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Nguyen wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 7.36 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 3.88,
        "options": [
            3.88,
            7.36,
            38.8,
            3.98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 7. When the sun is at 19 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            3,
            3,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 16 ohms and 43 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            43,
            3,
            59,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 refrigerator, 22 fan, 97 cycles, 3 algae spots, and 13 snail? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            100,
            17,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Campbell wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 5cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            9,
            39,
            8,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 flower vase, 43 sofa, 86 mat, 9 fungi spots, and 3 dog? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 130,
        "options": [
            95,
            130,
            44,
            131
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            0,
            8,
            14,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 33000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 279000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            76,
            401,
            118.28,
            868
        ],
        "answer": 118.28
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 39. When the sun is at 112 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            70,
            28,
            61,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 26 miles in 8 hours and 60 minutes?",
        "options": [
            4.622222222222223,
            8.297520513024399,
            8.606329988826712,
            4.2543019174280055
        ],
        "answer": 4.622222222222223
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 29 apples , how many apples can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            29,
            16,
            45,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            20,
            -23,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 tubelight, 25 broom, 92 flower vase, 3 crows, and 2 fungi spots? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 110,
        "options": [
            110,
            129,
            129,
            128
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 mat, 63 chair, 28 fan, 12 trees, and 1 cat? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            17,
            37,
            42,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 sofa, 84 couch, 55 pair of shoes, 11 fungi spots, and 12 human beings? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            24,
            23,
            66,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 cycles, 75 bed, 7 sofa, 2 snail, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            84,
            83,
            76,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 refrigerator, 5 bed, 45 couch, 8 pigeons, and 7 dog? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            20,
            53,
            16,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wells wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 27cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            36,
            24,
            34,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 9 ohms and 12 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            21,
            21,
            108,
            7,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Graham wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 4.67 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 3.35,
        "options": [
            3.45,
            33.5,
            3.35,
            4.67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 64. When the sun is at 118 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            84,
            103,
            34,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 33 ohms and 9 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            297,
            0,
            42,
            6,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Parker wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 21cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            30,
            6,
            7,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            14,
            4,
            3,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 14 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 17 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            27,
            36,
            378,
            41,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Parker wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 6.747 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 2.85,
        "options": [
            6.747,
            2.95,
            28.5,
            2.85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 37.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            355,
            116.0,
            383,
            252
        ],
        "answer": 116.0
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 4.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            320,
            30.6,
            33,
            367
        ],
        "answer": 30.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnold began counting from 0. She skip-counted by nine's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 270,
        "options": [
            0,
            272,
            270,
            271
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -11,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            0,
            5,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            10,
            -25,
            15,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 2000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 24000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            295,
            764,
            83333.333,
            405
        ],
        "answer": 83333.333
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 table, 7 refrigerator, 53 bed, 2 human beings, and 15 snail? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            80,
            88,
            72,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 bed, 57 table, 12 fan, 13 fungi spots, and 9 people? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            25,
            66,
            79,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 11 apples , how many apples can a man eat?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            11,
            30,
            41,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 tubelight, 25 broom, 92 flower vase, 3 crows, and 2 fungi spots? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 124,
        "options": [
            32,
            95,
            125,
            124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            5,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Gibson increased from 486 per month to 598 per month while the salary of Taylor increased from 415 to 753 and of Johnson increased from 608 to 949 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Johnson",
        "options": [
            "Gibson",
            "Taylor",
            "Johnson",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 tubelight, 43 couch, 65 table, 4 people, and 9 plants? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            126,
            129,
            122,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            14,
            11,
            25,
            -25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 2 feet by 2 feet?",
        "options": [
            6442,
            576,
            8288,
            2375
        ],
        "answer": 576
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 1 cake , how many cake can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            1,
            9,
            10,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Baker wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 8cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            29,
            13,
            36,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Allen wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 24cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            17,
            17,
            29,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 tubelight, 25 broom, 92 flower vase, 3 crows, and 2 fungi spots? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            47,
            273,
            0,
            337
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 52 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/7 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            75,
            60,
            22.29,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 22.29
    },
    {
        "question": "Jenkins began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 164,
        "options": [
            165,
            0,
            164,
            166
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Diya wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 25cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            33,
            4,
            4,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 34 empty boxes, 17 table, 4 algae spots, and 5 cockroaches? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            58,
            52,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 29.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            414,
            473,
            125.6,
            204
        ],
        "answer": 125.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Coleman wants to put a car in a road.The road is 6.648 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 3.95,
        "options": [
            3.95,
            39.5,
            4.05,
            6.648
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            -25,
            25,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 67 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 4/6 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            38,
            20,
            95,
            44.67
        ],
        "answer": 44.67
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 sofa, 83 broom, 23 pair of shoes, 13 snail, and 12 fungi spots? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            104,
            56,
            133
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a tuesday and returns to the bank 11years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Saturday",
            "tuesday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wagner wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 23cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            37,
            37,
            25,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 16 years old in the year 1875.In his greatest win, he looted 90381059 of 1820892505 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1880,
            1899,
            1859,
            1886
        ],
        "answer": 1859
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            8,
            26,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 45.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            265,
            179.4,
            218,
            258
        ],
        "answer": 179.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Morgan wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 40cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            44,
            18,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jackson wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 15cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            29,
            6,
            26,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -19,
            18,
            19,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "Holmes wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 32cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            29,
            10,
            29,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            8,
            26,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Anvi wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 5.854 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 1.37,
        "options": [
            1.4700000000000002,
            13.700000000000001,
            1.37,
            5.854
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stephens wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 9cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            11,
            8,
            30,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 13.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            109.4,
            322,
            463,
            462
        ],
        "answer": 109.4
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 14 watermelon , how many watermelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            14,
            22,
            36,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            8,
            26,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 7 ohms and 29 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            36,
            7,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 98. When the sun is at 84 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            105,
            109,
            31,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 mat, 63 chair, 28 fan, 12 trees, and 1 cat? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            99,
            100,
            40,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 3 feet by 10 feet?",
        "options": [
            582,
            5216,
            2871,
            4320
        ],
        "answer": 4320
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 sofa, 83 broom, 23 pair of shoes, 13 snail, and 12 fungi spots? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 115,
        "options": [
            116,
            36,
            92,
            115
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            4,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wells wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 7.283 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 6.03,
        "options": [
            6.03,
            6.13,
            7.283,
            60.300000000000004
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 fan, 33 empty boxes, 30 tubelight, 2 dog, and 12 cat? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            15,
            32,
            44,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dixon wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 5cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            7,
            28,
            40,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 2 men, 9 women, 2 children of less than 10 years, 4 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            111,
            17,
            0,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 chair, 39 couch, 5 bed, 13 people, and 11 algae spots? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            48,
            67,
            8,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 43 ohms and 30 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            43,
            6,
            30,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 7 men, 7 women, 9 children of less than 10 years, 7 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            112,
            30,
            0,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcdonald wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 8.205 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 2.76,
        "options": [
            8.205,
            27.599999999999998,
            2.86,
            2.76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 24 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 25 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            43,
            19,
            25,
            456,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 28.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            58.4,
            149,
            433,
            188
        ],
        "answer": 58.4
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 9 sofa, 93 couch, 11 people, and 7 cockroaches? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            71,
            68,
            103,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 34 miles in 10 hours and 53 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.05206738131699847,
            2.6711034104953417,
            3.370213943800571,
            8.495303252415198
        ],
        "answer": 0.05206738131699847
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 55 miles in 9 hours and 8 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.7996391571283,
            6.021897810218978,
            5.273062440381134,
            4.854197717246839
        ],
        "answer": 6.021897810218978
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 72000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 685000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            909,
            917,
            559,
            105.109
        ],
        "answer": 105.109
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 5 feet by 5 feet?",
        "options": [
            8873,
            716,
            3600,
            5199
        ],
        "answer": 3600
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            1,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Simpson wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 5cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            8,
            8,
            4,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 broom, 23 fan, 5 couch, 10 algae spots, and 5 trees? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            34,
            40,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 21 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            6,
            11,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 34.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            277.2,
            437,
            347,
            349
        ],
        "answer": 277.2
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 8000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 904000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            395,
            8.85,
            248,
            621
        ],
        "answer": 8.85
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 42 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 16 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            42,
            16,
            1848,
            43,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 14 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            4,
            -11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 59 miles in 6 hours and 1 minutes?",
        "options": [
            15.689750692520777,
            7.062944418245308,
            3.998760033818587,
            9.021779166097383
        ],
        "answer": 15.689750692520777
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 49 ohms and 47 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            5,
            96,
            47,
            2303,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 84000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 457000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            92,
            891,
            958,
            0.184
        ],
        "answer": 0.184
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 50 fan, 58 sofa, 4 cat, and 3 dog? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            8,
            7,
            62,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 63000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 269000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            342,
            693,
            234.201,
            604
        ],
        "answer": 234.201
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 tubelight, 43 couch, 65 table, 4 people, and 9 plants? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            85,
            22,
            5,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 21 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            6,
            11,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 tubelight, 43 couch, 65 table, 4 people, and 9 plants? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            69,
            13,
            52,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 78000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 355000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            200,
            0.22,
            846,
            999
        ],
        "answer": 0.22
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 18 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            24,
            12,
            -24
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1446.In his greatest win, he looted 433358927 of 4817350492 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1896,
            1789,
            1898,
            1434
        ],
        "answer": 1434
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 41 ohms and 30 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            7,
            71,
            1230,
            0,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 5 feet by 1 feet?",
        "options": [
            9124,
            720,
            795,
            4769
        ],
        "answer": 720
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 25.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            387,
            460,
            151.0,
            331
        ],
        "answer": 151.0
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Castillo increased from 469 per month to 980 per month while the salary of Weaver increased from 967 to 998 and of Fernandez increased from 409 to 899 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Fernandez",
        "options": [
            "Castillo",
            "Weaver",
            "Fernandez",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Baker wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 13cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            29,
            36,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            30,
            13,
            17,
            -30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 30 flower vase, 24 sofa, 2 plants, and 2 dog? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            26,
            4,
            43,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 26 apples , how many apples can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            26,
            6,
            32,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jackson wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 6.692 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 5.37,
        "options": [
            5.37,
            5.47,
            6.692,
            53.7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            20,
            11,
            9,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anaya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            0,
            84,
            85,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 27. When the sun is at 46 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            46,
            27,
            22,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Peterson wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 14cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            32,
            15,
            22,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wilson wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 9.359 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 6.58,
        "options": [
            6.68,
            9.359,
            6.58,
            65.8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 7 ohms and 29 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            7,
            36,
            10,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            19,
            7,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 142 grapes , how many grapes can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            142,
            67,
            209,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 pair of shoes, 67 chair, 8 bed, 12 plants, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            98,
            86,
            86,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 51000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 112000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            80,
            455.357,
            403,
            589
        ],
        "answer": 455.357
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            16,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            14,
            11,
            25,
            -25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            4,
            0,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lewis wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 9.215 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 2.22,
        "options": [
            22.200000000000003,
            2.22,
            9.215,
            2.3200000000000003
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 cycles, 77 empty boxes, 12 bed, 4 human beings, and 11 cat? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            82,
            95,
            16,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 12 ohms and 49 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            12,
            8,
            49,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 8 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            10,
            0,
            15,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 21 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            48,
            8,
            21,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnold earns $13 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $3 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Arnold was paid $2080, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            262,
            253,
            148,
            387
        ],
        "answer": 148
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 couch, 63 tubelight, 44 empty boxes, 14 dog, and 15 people? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            58,
            76,
            30,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 91 miles in 7 hours and 35 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.518749985669151,
            1.119034617285859,
            0.32,
            7.167213040761449
        ],
        "answer": 0.32
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 29 sofa, 61 tubelight, 4 snail, and 12 dog? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            84,
            37,
            104,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 105 grapes , how many grapes can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            105,
            57,
            162,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 cycles, 77 empty boxes, 12 bed, 4 human beings, and 11 cat? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            93,
            64,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            26,
            13,
            14,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 69 broom, 92 mat, 1 cockroaches, and 8 cat? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 162,
        "options": [
            70,
            93,
            162,
            163
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 empty boxes, 60 cycles, 58 refrigerator, 1 pigeons, and 11 trees? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            139,
            136,
            136,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 48000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 418000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            710,
            482,
            0.115,
            672
        ],
        "answer": 0.115
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 tubelight, 25 broom, 92 flower vase, 3 crows, and 2 fungi spots? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            32,
            95,
            6,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 pair of shoes, 67 chair, 8 bed, 12 plants, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            86,
            20,
            85,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anika wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 7.529 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 1.05,
        "options": [
            7.529,
            1.05,
            1.1500000000000001,
            10.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 sofa, 83 broom, 23 pair of shoes, 13 snail, and 12 fungi spots? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 97,
        "options": [
            133,
            128,
            137,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 86000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 197000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            416,
            24,
            436.548,
            764
        ],
        "answer": 436.548
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 41.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            288,
            213,
            167.8,
            359
        ],
        "answer": 167.8
    },
    {
        "question": "Gomez wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 40cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            5,
            14,
            7,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 31.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            431,
            463,
            263,
            252.8
        ],
        "answer": 252.8
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -28,
            28,
            22,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 23000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 617000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            511,
            213,
            37.277,
            564
        ],
        "answer": 37.277
    },
    {
        "question": "Eva wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 9cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            12,
            28,
            24,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            2,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 36 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/10 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            10.8,
            37,
            92,
            65
        ],
        "answer": 10.8
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            4,
            0,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 24 watermelon , how many watermelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            24,
            10,
            34,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mohammed wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 16cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            21,
            25,
            3,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Barnes wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 6.472 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 4.33,
        "options": [
            43.3,
            4.33,
            4.43,
            6.472
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 26. When the sun is at 97 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            45,
            5,
            33,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            0,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1828.In his greatest win, he looted 493777475 of 5479028182 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1889,
            1816,
            1885,
            1851
        ],
        "answer": 1816
    },
    {
        "question": "Bennett wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 19cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            23,
            26,
            30,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Darsh wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 5.2 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 2.91,
        "options": [
            3.0100000000000002,
            5.2,
            2.91,
            29.1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hicks wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 39cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            12,
            7,
            22,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 22 watermelon , how many watermelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            22,
            28,
            50,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 bed, 33 cycles, 47 table, 12 snail, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            25,
            59,
            24,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 41 miles in 2 hours and 41 minutes?",
        "options": [
            24.447204968944103,
            8.39958772765912,
            8.388487416950639,
            1.5051525927226785
        ],
        "answer": 24.447204968944103
    },
    {
        "question": "Perry began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            0,
            122,
            121,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ross began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 284,
        "options": [
            0,
            285,
            284,
            286
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -24,
            24,
            4,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 89 miles in 5 hours and 29 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.164438010083453,
            3.55085820176687,
            8.443542774578395,
            0.4328267477203648
        ],
        "answer": 0.4328267477203648
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 24 chocolates , how many chocolates can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            24,
            20,
            44,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 broom, 33 refrigerator, 41 pair of shoes, 8 cat, and 11 human beings? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 81,
        "options": [
            97,
            106,
            104,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 flower vase, 52 mat, 10 couch, 1 cockroaches, and 3 human beings? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            60,
            166,
            163,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ramos began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 560,
        "options": [
            0,
            561,
            562,
            560
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 11 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            2,
            7,
            6,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 37 tubelight, 38 cycles, 12 crows, and 10 snail? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            52,
            1,
            72,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            19,
            7,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "Knight wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 35cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            42,
            35,
            44,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 8 ohms and 12 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            20,
            5,
            8,
            96,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            7,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Pari wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 17cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            17,
            32,
            23,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 19 ohms and 36 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 16 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            16,
            55,
            45,
            684,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 37 miles in 9 hours and 12 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.819158209752066,
            6.089318977920772,
            0.06702898550724638,
            8.334741360177494
        ],
        "answer": 0.06702898550724638
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 refrigerator, 22 fan, 97 cycles, 3 algae spots, and 13 snail? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            100,
            17,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 51. When the sun is at 75 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            8,
            109,
            98,
            102
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 bed, 57 table, 12 fan, 13 fungi spots, and 9 people? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            66,
            78,
            25,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 22.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            312,
            286,
            93.0,
            469
        ],
        "answer": 93.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 13 years old in the year 1175.In his greatest win, he looted 870558767 of 9704542670 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1363,
            1162,
            1342,
            1777
        ],
        "answer": 1162
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 21 miles in 7 hours and 49 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.04477611940298507,
            9.932684942098458,
            5.466786199585865,
            1.7603300380619287
        ],
        "answer": 0.04477611940298507
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            4,
            1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 14 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            4,
            -11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 11 watermelon , how many watermelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            11,
            13,
            24,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Patterson wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 7cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            16,
            17,
            17,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            8,
            26,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 fan, 33 empty boxes, 30 tubelight, 2 dog, and 12 cat? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            32,
            44,
            75,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 6 watermelon , how many watermelon can a man eat?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            6,
            21,
            27,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 chair, 96 pair of shoes, 13 bed, 1 crows, and 5 human beings? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            267,
            199,
            0,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Porter wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 36cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            15,
            40,
            12,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 33 ohms and 44 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 14 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            44,
            77,
            1452,
            14,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 3 cake , how many cake can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            3,
            8,
            11,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 26 ohms and 5 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 1 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            31,
            1,
            26,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 flower vase, 43 sofa, 86 mat, 9 fungi spots, and 3 dog? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            39,
            33,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 40 cycles, 8 fan, 7 human beings, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            29,
            68,
            59,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 7 lemons , how many lemons can a man eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            7,
            16,
            23,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 34 empty boxes, 17 table, 4 algae spots, and 5 cockroaches? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            21,
            9,
            10,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 8 men, 4 women, 2 children of less than 10 years, 2 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            111,
            16,
            0,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 14 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            41,
            0,
            378,
            4,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Baker wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 29cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            4,
            9,
            21,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Henderson wants to put a house in a street.The street is 6.215 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 1.44,
        "options": [
            1.44,
            14.399999999999999,
            6.215,
            1.54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 20. When the sun is at 99 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            39,
            22,
            31,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $84 to the charity and a total of $9084 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            729,
            493,
            108,
            223
        ],
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 13.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            93.2,
            362,
            329,
            235
        ],
        "answer": 93.2
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 9years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "Saturday",
            "Friday",
            "Sunday",
            "Thursday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 flower vase, 52 mat, 10 couch, 1 cockroaches, and 3 human beings? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            57,
            11,
            5,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Porter wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 32cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            45,
            3,
            20,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reed earns $10 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $4 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Reed was paid $3511, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            459,
            476,
            363,
            279
        ],
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "Hawkins wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 39cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            45,
            17,
            24,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            2,
            -27,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 mat, 40 couch, 77 cycles, 4 plants, and 14 cat? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            41,
            118,
            81,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 14 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            4,
            -11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            5,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 28 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            28,
            6,
            34,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 24 tubelight, 86 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 11 crows? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            37,
            15,
            14,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 27.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            484,
            364,
            83.0,
            295
        ],
        "answer": 83.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Martin wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 17cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            3,
            8,
            34,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 62000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 12000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            5166.667,
            723,
            875,
            891
        ],
        "answer": 5166.667
    },
    {
        "question": "Advaith wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 32cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            20,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            3,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -24,
            24,
            4,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 29 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            18,
            47,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 mat, 63 chair, 28 fan, 12 trees, and 1 cat? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            278,
            322,
            3,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 table, 58 empty boxes, 12 flower vase, 5 fungi spots, and 1 trees? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            31,
            156,
            138,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Jackson increased from 501 per month to 502 per month while the salary of Aditya increased from 633 to 720 and of Edwards increased from 710 to 789 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Edwards",
        "options": [
            "Jackson",
            "Aditya",
            "Edwards",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            19,
            7,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "Murray wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 5.943 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 1.4,
        "options": [
            14.0,
            5.943,
            1.5,
            1.4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 6 feet?",
        "options": [
            3456,
            9182,
            8282,
            6573
        ],
        "answer": 3456
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 12000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 355000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            658,
            33802.817,
            355,
            660
        ],
        "answer": 33802.817
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            27,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 6 feet by 5 feet?",
        "options": [
            9291,
            679,
            8309,
            4320
        ],
        "answer": 4320
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 fan, 33 empty boxes, 30 tubelight, 2 dog, and 12 cat? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            62,
            39,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 flower vase, 52 mat, 10 couch, 1 cockroaches, and 3 human beings? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            37,
            2,
            71,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 37 ohms and 38 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1406,
            4,
            2,
            0,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Medina wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 11cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            12,
            25,
            44,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Crawford began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            53,
            52,
            0,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rose wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 24cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            2,
            40,
            28,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Warren wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 4.42 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 1.03,
        "options": [
            4.42,
            10.3,
            1.03,
            1.1300000000000001
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 35 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            4,
            9,
            0,
            1540,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 12 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            12,
            20,
            32,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $68 to the charity and a total of $17340 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            543,
            255,
            87,
            458
        ],
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            12,
            6,
            5,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Crawford wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 6.354 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 3.34,
        "options": [
            33.4,
            3.34,
            3.44,
            6.354
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 84000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 647000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            643,
            687,
            900,
            0.13
        ],
        "answer": 0.13
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -28,
            28,
            22,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnold began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 292,
        "options": [
            294,
            293,
            292,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 67 pair of shoes, 94 bed, 9 cockroaches, and 13 crows? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 165,
        "options": [
            166,
            71,
            165,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $24 to the charity and a total of $6330 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            33,
            214,
            637,
            263
        ],
        "answer": 263
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            3,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            14,
            11,
            25,
            -25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Reyansh wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 7.041 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 4.44,
        "options": [
            7.041,
            44.400000000000006,
            4.54,
            4.44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 24.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            216.9,
            306,
            374,
            462
        ],
        "answer": 216.9
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 flower vase, 95 pair of shoes, 31 sofa, 11 dog, and 6 snail? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            74,
            134,
            137,
            140
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 36000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 739000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            537,
            61,
            48.714,
            380
        ],
        "answer": 48.714
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -19,
            18,
            19,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 93 miles in 8 hours and 60 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.3965012106357721,
            0.27555555555555555,
            6.2559971942361905,
            5.729497160251837
        ],
        "answer": 0.27555555555555555
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            0,
            7,
            11,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 2000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 365000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            335,
            10,
            704,
            5.479
        ],
        "answer": 5.479
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 12 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            0,
            30,
            9,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 37 tubelight, 38 cycles, 12 crows, and 10 snail? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            5,
            19,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            0,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Washington wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 20cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            14,
            24,
            29,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 sofa, 61 table, 63 bed, 8 snail, and 10 fungi spots? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 125,
        "options": [
            71,
            125,
            126,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 chair, 26 pair of shoes, 88 cycles, 15 cockroaches, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            280,
            356,
            52,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 90 miles in 2 hours and 11 minutes?",
        "options": [
            65.95419847328245,
            4.707302745554545,
            9.403678712140277,
            8.681749744189482
        ],
        "answer": 65.95419847328245
    },
    {
        "question": "Martinez wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 31cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            7,
            38,
            38,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 26 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            26,
            18,
            44,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 49 ohms and 47 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            7,
            0,
            96,
            2303
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Clark wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 9cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            20,
            6,
            4,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Washington wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 5.576 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 1.35,
        "options": [
            1.4500000000000002,
            5.576,
            13.5,
            1.35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Evans earns $8 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $3 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Evans was paid $3075, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            28,
            306,
            421,
            206
        ],
        "answer": 306
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $56 to the charity and a total of $6096 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            248,
            108,
            301,
            195
        ],
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 30 miles in 8 hours and 36 minutes?",
        "options": [
            4.049191810875595,
            0.09302325581395349,
            8.410364208025772,
            6.963158576716367
        ],
        "answer": 0.09302325581395349
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 13000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 958000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            864,
            434,
            399,
            0.014
        ],
        "answer": 0.014
    },
    {
        "question": "Nichols wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 26cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            20,
            36,
            40,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $74 to the charity and a total of $4080 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            940,
            222,
            1000,
            55
        ],
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 3 sofa, 13 pair of shoes, 5 cat, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            20,
            21,
            16,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 68 miles in 7 hours and 23 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.4267976464988035,
            9.209932279909706,
            9.54125053942354,
            6.238128934068926
        ],
        "answer": 9.209932279909706
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 18 years old in the year 1734.In his greatest win, he looted 984626862 of 1791178653 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1872,
            1716,
            1757,
            1865
        ],
        "answer": 1716
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            5,
            -16,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Weaver wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 32cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            34,
            9,
            12,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            30,
            13,
            17,
            -30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Sullivan wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 9.539 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 5.26,
        "options": [
            52.599999999999994,
            5.359999999999999,
            5.26,
            9.539
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            0,
            6,
            7,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -24,
            24,
            4,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 43 ohms and 30 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            73,
            30,
            6,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 flower vase, 33 table, 84 cycles, 15 pigeons, and 8 human beings? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 132,
        "options": [
            99,
            48,
            133,
            132
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            14,
            11,
            25,
            -25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            30,
            13,
            17,
            -30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 couch, 63 tubelight, 44 empty boxes, 14 dog, and 15 people? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            130,
            146,
            147,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            5,
            18,
            8,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Turner wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 16cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            24,
            8,
            34,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 pair of shoes, 19 bed, 60 tubelight, 5 cockroaches, and 15 cat? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            31,
            21,
            20,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Edwards wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 5.25 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 2.48,
        "options": [
            2.48,
            5.25,
            2.58,
            24.8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 40 ohms and 31 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            4,
            0,
            71,
            1240,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            5,
            -26,
            21,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Robinson began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 400,
        "options": [
            0,
            401,
            400,
            402
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 34.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            214,
            437,
            143.2,
            317
        ],
        "answer": 143.2
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 tubelight, 89 empty boxes, 24 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 7 plants? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            101,
            10,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 18.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            126.1,
            499,
            212,
            190
        ],
        "answer": 126.1
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            14,
            30,
            15,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 8 cake , how many cake can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            8,
            9,
            17,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            -27,
            22,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -19,
            18,
            19,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            16,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Crawford wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 7.387 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 4.04,
        "options": [
            7.387,
            40.4,
            4.14,
            4.04
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 cycles, 77 empty boxes, 12 bed, 4 human beings, and 11 cat? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            16,
            15,
            82,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aditya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 225,
        "options": [
            227,
            225,
            0,
            226
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 41 grapes , how many grapes can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            41,
            79,
            120,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 refrigerator, 22 fan, 97 cycles, 3 algae spots, and 13 snail? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            107,
            126,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 18 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            24,
            12,
            -24
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 pair of shoes, 67 chair, 8 bed, 12 plants, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            288,
            0,
            39,
            267
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 13 ohms and 25 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            13,
            25,
            38,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wells wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 13cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            25,
            4,
            15,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 68000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 829000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            837,
            188,
            82.027,
            901
        ],
        "answer": 82.027
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 14cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            24,
            15,
            24,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 6 ohms and 32 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            192,
            0,
            38,
            10,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Patel wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 10cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            22,
            38,
            4,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            2,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stevens wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 31cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            17,
            39,
            43,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 4 cake , how many cake can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            4,
            2,
            6,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Navya earns $10 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Navya was paid $3715, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            346,
            290,
            70,
            380
        ],
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            9,
            0,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Robertson wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 14cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            17,
            13,
            4,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 82 miles in 8 hours and 47 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.038923168862075,
            7.072680074089936,
            9.335863377609108,
            4.7126811136732405
        ],
        "answer": 9.335863377609108
    },
    {
        "question": "Fisher wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 8.865 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 4.46,
        "options": [
            44.6,
            4.56,
            4.46,
            8.865
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gonzalez wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 9cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            3,
            12,
            35,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Morris began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            12,
            0,
            14,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 43 ohms and 30 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            27,
            1290,
            6,
            73,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 flower vase, 43 sofa, 86 mat, 9 fungi spots, and 3 dog? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            215,
            377,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 34 empty boxes, 17 table, 4 algae spots, and 5 cockroaches? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            61,
            8,
            65,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 50 ohms and 47 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 12 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            12,
            2350,
            97,
            25,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 15 chocolates , how many chocolates can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            15,
            24,
            39,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 empty boxes, 73 flower vase, 53 mat, 10 fungi spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 131,
        "options": [
            131,
            132,
            63,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 8 cake , how many cake can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            8,
            10,
            18,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            15,
            9,
            8,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 14 ohms and 22 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            36,
            3,
            308,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 6.827 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 5.46,
        "options": [
            6.827,
            5.56,
            54.6,
            5.46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            1,
            8,
            9,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            7,
            5,
            4,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 45000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 747000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            766,
            60240.964,
            73,
            773
        ],
        "answer": 60240.964
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            5,
            -25,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Gardner wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 25cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            2,
            7,
            31,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hunt wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 33cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            24,
            10,
            43,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Simmons began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 518,
        "options": [
            519,
            518,
            0,
            520
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 5 feet by 3 feet?",
        "options": [
            2361,
            3480,
            6518,
            2160
        ],
        "answer": 2160
    },
    {
        "question": "Weaver wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 12cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            22,
            16,
            24,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 22 chocolates , how many chocolates can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            22,
            7,
            29,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -19,
            18,
            19,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1497.In his greatest win, he looted 567053171 of 5658052756 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1760,
            1477,
            1539,
            1700
        ],
        "answer": 1477
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 43 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            70,
            27,
            43,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            2,
            -27,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Anya wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 6.249 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 4.04,
        "options": [
            4.04,
            4.14,
            6.249,
            40.4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 7 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            7,
            8,
            15,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Morris began counting from 0. She skip-counted by nine's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 828,
        "options": [
            0,
            828,
            830,
            829
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 chair, 7 tubelight, 2 bed, 9 algae spots, and 12 dog? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            15,
            12,
            14,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 42000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 274000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            907,
            192,
            153.285,
            911
        ],
        "answer": 153.285
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 35.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            316,
            488,
            277,
            71.4
        ],
        "answer": 71.4
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 41.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            206,
            282,
            383,
            91.4
        ],
        "answer": 91.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Cole began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 800,
        "options": [
            800,
            801,
            802,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 3years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Monday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Monday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bennett wants to put a car in a road.The road is 6.028 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 3.1,
        "options": [
            31.0,
            6.028,
            3.2,
            3.1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Powell wants to put a house in a street.The street is 7.58 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 6.08,
        "options": [
            7.58,
            6.18,
            6.08,
            60.8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 63 miles in 6 hours and 35 minutes?",
        "options": [
            15.311392405063293,
            8.898436571885082,
            1.5008819103393327,
            4.670214345299232
        ],
        "answer": 15.311392405063293
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -28,
            28,
            22,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "White wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 35cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            40,
            42,
            23,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 3.462 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 1.13,
        "options": [
            1.13,
            3.462,
            11.299999999999999,
            1.23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 broom, 23 fan, 5 couch, 10 algae spots, and 5 trees? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            16,
            15,
            15,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Warren wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 40cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            26,
            41,
            26,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 11 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            11,
            30,
            41,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Barnes wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 9cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            6,
            37,
            2,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 fan, 33 empty boxes, 30 tubelight, 2 dog, and 12 cat? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            83,
            79,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reynolds began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 616,
        "options": [
            616,
            0,
            618,
            617
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 13 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            28,
            25,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 bed, 57 table, 12 fan, 13 fungi spots, and 9 people? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            66,
            23,
            25,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Meyer earns $18 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $4 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Meyer was paid $3655, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            184,
            197,
            457,
            177
        ],
        "answer": 184
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 94 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/7 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            57,
            40.29,
            11,
            46
        ],
        "answer": 40.29
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 22. When the sun is at 165 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            2,
            77,
            9,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 13 years old in the year 1150.In his greatest win, he looted 301138350 of 4809177556 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1213,
            1137,
            1517,
            1210
        ],
        "answer": 1137
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 17 ohms and 7 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            119,
            24,
            7,
            35,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            2,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 35 ohms and 21 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            56,
            21,
            35,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 24.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            149.6,
            235,
            487,
            210
        ],
        "answer": 149.6
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            3,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Sunday and returns to the bank 11years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Thursday",
        "options": [
            "Friday",
            "tuesday",
            "Saturday",
            "Thursday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bennett began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 432,
        "options": [
            432,
            0,
            434,
            433
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 flower vase, 33 table, 84 cycles, 15 pigeons, and 8 human beings? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            48,
            24,
            23,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sullivan wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 21cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            13,
            13,
            17,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 3years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Sunday",
        "options": [
            "Monday",
            "Saturday",
            "Sunday",
            "Wednesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 6 men, 2 women, 5 children of less than 10 years, 10 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            116,
            23,
            0,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 30 ohms and 10 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 13 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            13,
            28,
            10,
            40,
            300
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcdonald wants to put a house in a street.The street is 3.8 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 2.72,
        "options": [
            3.8,
            2.72,
            27.200000000000003,
            2.8200000000000003
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 21 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            6,
            11,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 chair, 39 couch, 5 bed, 13 people, and 11 algae spots? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            25,
            24,
            50,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            4,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 37 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            20,
            8,
            18,
            55,
            666
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 36.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            139,
            345,
            72.4,
            245
        ],
        "answer": 72.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 5years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "tuesday",
        "options": [
            "Friday",
            "Thursday",
            "tuesday",
            "Monday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 21 ohms and 46 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 24 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            966,
            46,
            67,
            24,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 51. When the sun is at 150 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            49,
            43,
            62,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hamilton wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 20cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            30,
            26,
            43,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 11 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            8,
            21,
            7,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnold wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 3.986 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 2.37,
        "options": [
            3.986,
            2.47,
            23.700000000000003,
            2.37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hughes wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 28cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            17,
            36,
            3,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 36 ohms and 39 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 21 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            75,
            21,
            39,
            1404,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 23 watermelon , how many watermelon can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            23,
            28,
            51,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 tubelight, 89 empty boxes, 24 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 7 plants? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            61,
            2,
            66,
            104
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 broom, 33 refrigerator, 41 pair of shoes, 8 cat, and 11 human beings? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            89,
            49,
            47,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 9 cake , how many cake can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            9,
            3,
            12,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 26 ohms and 5 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            5,
            26,
            31,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 83. When the sun is at 9 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            106,
            62,
            62,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            3,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 87000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 156000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            931,
            557.692,
            420,
            834
        ],
        "answer": 557.692
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 2 feet by 5 feet?",
        "options": [
            9492,
            6778,
            5425,
            1440
        ],
        "answer": 1440
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 14 years old in the year 1129.In his greatest win, he looted 420047200 of 5243366945 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1827,
            1403,
            1220,
            1115
        ],
        "answer": 1115
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            30,
            13,
            17,
            -30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Grant wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 16cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            21,
            10,
            22,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 66 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 4/10 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            86,
            86,
            26.4,
            56
        ],
        "answer": 26.4
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 26. When the sun is at 40 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            11,
            16,
            19,
            106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 16 miles in 4 hours and 57 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.05387205387205387,
            9.282940822127758,
            2.5657768620196926,
            7.274580285639393
        ],
        "answer": 0.05387205387205387
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 31.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            98.4,
            358,
            279,
            316
        ],
        "answer": 98.4
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 9 sofa, 93 couch, 11 people, and 7 cockroaches? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 91,
        "options": [
            386,
            0,
            329,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            20,
            -23,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 16 lemons , how many lemons can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            16,
            27,
            43,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 empty boxes, 60 cycles, 58 refrigerator, 1 pigeons, and 11 trees? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            0,
            339,
            64,
            287
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 71 miles in 3 hours and 30 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.716344797795252,
            9.936082638015115,
            32.457142857142856,
            9.01677205344125
        ],
        "answer": 32.457142857142856
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 6 cake , how many cake can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            6,
            7,
            13,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 27 watermelon , how many watermelon can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            27,
            10,
            37,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 7.214 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 2.36,
        "options": [
            2.46,
            23.599999999999998,
            7.214,
            2.36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Diya wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 33cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            34,
            10,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 5 feet by 2 feet?",
        "options": [
            5674,
            228,
            9152,
            1440
        ],
        "answer": 1440
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 tubelight, 89 empty boxes, 24 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 7 plants? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            10,
            26,
            101,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 25 chair, 99 fan, 3 snail, and 5 trees? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            0,
            283,
            139,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 108 grapes , how many grapes can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            108,
            83,
            191,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 23 watermelon , how many watermelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            23,
            22,
            45,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 mat, 40 couch, 77 cycles, 4 plants, and 14 cat? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            118,
            81,
            41,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 27 apples , how many apples can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            27,
            22,
            49,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 14 watermelon , how many watermelon can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            14,
            23,
            37,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 10 feet?",
        "options": [
            5760,
            9360,
            130,
            9261
        ],
        "answer": 5760
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 pair of shoes, 67 chair, 8 bed, 12 plants, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            58,
            13,
            10,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            2,
            -27,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -11,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 3 sofa, 13 pair of shoes, 5 cat, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            34,
            7,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 chair, 96 pair of shoes, 13 bed, 1 crows, and 5 human beings? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 122,
        "options": [
            14,
            109,
            122,
            123
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ananya wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 3.388 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 1.64,
        "options": [
            1.64,
            3.388,
            1.74,
            16.4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 18 years old in the year 1348.In his greatest win, he looted 194986504 of 7405415968 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1330,
            1351,
            1854,
            1615
        ],
        "answer": 1330
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 18 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            18,
            29,
            47,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 13 years old in the year 1478.In his greatest win, he looted 328818921 of 3979477743 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1823,
            1607,
            1765,
            1465
        ],
        "answer": 1465
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 41 ohms and 30 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            71,
            30,
            8,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wright wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 7.112 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 1.58,
        "options": [
            1.58,
            15.8,
            7.112,
            1.6800000000000002
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            21,
            2,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 12 bed, 39 cycles, 13 crows, and 6 cat? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            69,
            32,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 59 miles in 7 hours and 53 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.7236914787334316,
            0.12473572938689217,
            2.945970914400175,
            6.164876929522078
        ],
        "answer": 0.12473572938689217
    },
    {
        "question": "Wallace wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 6cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            9,
            5,
            25,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fernandez wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 9.644 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 4.79,
        "options": [
            47.9,
            4.89,
            4.79,
            9.644
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sanchez wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 9.612 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 2.79,
        "options": [
            27.9,
            9.612,
            2.79,
            2.89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mills wants to put a car in a road.The road is 5.871 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 2.7,
        "options": [
            2.7,
            2.8000000000000003,
            27.0,
            5.871
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 refrigerator, 5 bed, 45 couch, 8 pigeons, and 7 dog? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            54,
            11,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 19 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            9,
            10,
            15,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Perry wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 27cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            9,
            42,
            16,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hawkins wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 3.797 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 1.69,
        "options": [
            16.9,
            1.79,
            1.69,
            3.797
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            13,
            6,
            5,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            -25,
            25,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 26. When the sun is at 119 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            78,
            30,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 25 chair, 99 fan, 3 snail, and 5 trees? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 125,
        "options": [
            102,
            126,
            26,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 69 broom, 92 mat, 1 cockroaches, and 8 cat? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            35,
            142,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 12 bed, 39 cycles, 13 crows, and 6 cat? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            19,
            52,
            59,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 16 watermelon , how many watermelon can a man eat?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            16,
            19,
            35,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reyes wants to put a car in a road.The road is 7.142 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 1.18,
        "options": [
            1.28,
            11.799999999999999,
            7.142,
            1.18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 2 feet by 10 feet?",
        "options": [
            9376,
            2880,
            7354,
            2126
        ],
        "answer": 2880
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            7,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 78 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 5/6 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            70,
            65.0,
            31,
            96
        ],
        "answer": 65.0
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 37 tubelight, 38 cycles, 12 crows, and 10 snail? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            86,
            85,
            50,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 30 watermelon , how many watermelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            30,
            24,
            54,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 couch, 63 tubelight, 44 empty boxes, 14 dog, and 15 people? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            76,
            29,
            30,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -24,
            24,
            4,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 18 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            24,
            12,
            -24
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 21 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            6,
            11,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Washington wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 36cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            37,
            18,
            4,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Williams wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 13cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            7,
            13,
            17,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 29 sofa, 61 tubelight, 4 snail, and 12 dog? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            38,
            100,
            65,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 69 broom, 92 mat, 1 cockroaches, and 8 cat? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 162,
        "options": [
            93,
            162,
            163,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 29 watermelon , how many watermelon can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            29,
            20,
            49,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 46.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            354,
            447,
            280.2,
            342
        ],
        "answer": 280.2
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 45.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            267,
            94.6,
            132,
            217
        ],
        "answer": 94.6
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 chair, 39 couch, 5 bed, 13 people, and 11 algae spots? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            12,
            71,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aayan wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 3.328 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 1.79,
        "options": [
            3.328,
            1.79,
            17.9,
            1.8900000000000001
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Monday and returns to the bank 8years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "tuesday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "tuesday",
            "Saturday",
            "Wednesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 3 sofa, 13 pair of shoes, 5 cat, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            29,
            16,
            30,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 16 chocolates , how many chocolates can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            16,
            23,
            39,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            15,
            2,
            8,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 1 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            1008,
            6375,
            3034,
            5056
        ],
        "answer": 1008
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 bed, 43 broom, 43 refrigerator, 10 algae spots, and 12 pigeons? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            53,
            23,
            54,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 tubelight, 89 empty boxes, 24 refrigerator, 2 crows, and 7 plants? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 125,
        "options": [
            26,
            125,
            126,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Webb wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 26cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            2,
            15,
            7,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 21 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            6,
            11,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 table, 58 empty boxes, 12 flower vase, 5 fungi spots, and 1 trees? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            71,
            7,
            17,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 23 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            23,
            9,
            32,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -24,
            24,
            4,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 38 miles in 8 hours and 25 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.1203960396039604,
            4.370815331601863,
            7.3100101254905,
            1.5149267802310717
        ],
        "answer": 0.1203960396039604
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            5,
            -26,
            21,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            1,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 67 pair of shoes, 94 bed, 9 cockroaches, and 13 crows? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 132,
        "options": [
            295,
            132,
            0,
            275
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 2000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 674000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            708,
            980,
            0.003,
            72
        ],
        "answer": 0.003
    },
    {
        "question": "Olson wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 13cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            7,
            35,
            2,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 13 ohms and 45 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            58,
            585,
            4,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Prisha wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 25cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            26,
            4,
            33,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 9 sofa, 93 couch, 11 people, and 7 cockroaches? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 104,
        "options": [
            105,
            104,
            104,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 31. When the sun is at 57 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            60,
            25,
            108,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 3 sofa, 13 pair of shoes, 5 cat, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            18,
            21,
            16,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 79 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 5/8 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            100,
            91,
            49.38,
            58
        ],
        "answer": 49.38
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            0,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            27,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 49 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 5/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            81,
            42,
            27.22,
            81
        ],
        "answer": 27.22
    },
    {
        "question": "Mason wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 5.092 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 2.61,
        "options": [
            2.71,
            26.099999999999998,
            5.092,
            2.61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 97 miles in 7 hours and 41 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.082004224262331,
            2.8194831985206616,
            0.210412147505423,
            8.15288564858364
        ],
        "answer": 0.210412147505423
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 tubelight, 43 couch, 65 table, 4 people, and 9 plants? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            69,
            52,
            14,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 37 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            55,
            6,
            18,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            7,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 62 miles in 6 hours and 12 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.744181027518601,
            9.118096235604982,
            0.16666666666666666,
            5.552063639432945
        ],
        "answer": 0.16666666666666666
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayes wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 10cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            23,
            35,
            40,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 42 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            1848,
            0,
            86,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 table, 7 refrigerator, 53 bed, 2 human beings, and 15 snail? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            37,
            36,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Akshara wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 5.889 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 2.39,
        "options": [
            5.889,
            23.900000000000002,
            2.39,
            2.49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 3 sofa, 13 pair of shoes, 5 cat, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            166,
            29,
            262,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 98 miles in 4 hours and 48 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.346801739637101,
            7.775229114967176,
            0.3402777777777778,
            8.940036813072236
        ],
        "answer": 0.3402777777777778
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 13 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            28,
            25,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarush wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 22cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            30,
            18,
            26,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            -25,
            25,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            8,
            26,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Henderson wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 8.152 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 1.13,
        "options": [
            1.13,
            11.299999999999999,
            8.152,
            1.23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reyes wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 6.444 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 3.97,
        "options": [
            39.7,
            3.97,
            6.444,
            4.07
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 couch, 63 tubelight, 44 empty boxes, 14 dog, and 15 people? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            91,
            36,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 14 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            4,
            -11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "Riya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 235,
        "options": [
            0,
            236,
            237,
            235
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 16 lemons , how many lemons can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            16,
            9,
            25,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Carter wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 7.305 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 1.49,
        "options": [
            1.59,
            7.305,
            1.49,
            14.9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Iraa wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 25cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            22,
            35,
            29,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 41 ohms and 30 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 21 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            1230,
            21,
            30,
            71,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 29 watermelon , how many watermelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            29,
            24,
            53,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 sofa, 83 broom, 23 pair of shoes, 13 snail, and 12 fungi spots? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            36,
            92,
            25,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            10,
            6,
            0,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Morales wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 7.589 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 4.89,
        "options": [
            4.989999999999999,
            48.9,
            7.589,
            4.89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Medina wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 8.703 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 6.84,
        "options": [
            6.9399999999999995,
            68.4,
            6.84,
            8.703
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 77 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 4/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            29,
            16,
            97,
            34.22
        ],
        "answer": 34.22
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 7000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 188000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            530,
            59,
            37.234,
            518
        ],
        "answer": 37.234
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 10 feet by 9 feet?",
        "options": [
            9716,
            12960,
            5589,
            3514
        ],
        "answer": 12960
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 pair of shoes, 67 chair, 8 bed, 12 plants, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            13,
            77,
            14,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            7,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 2years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "tuesday",
            "Saturday",
            "Friday",
            "tuesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 20 chocolates , how many chocolates can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            20,
            12,
            32,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 4 cake , how many cake can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            4,
            10,
            14,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 67 miles in 7 hours and 50 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.2070812826394794,
            8.538588998127654,
            2.030284754184697,
            0.22808510638297874
        ],
        "answer": 0.22808510638297874
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            14,
            11,
            25,
            -25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Meyer wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 12cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            31,
            23,
            7,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 16 ohms and 43 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 16 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            43,
            36,
            59,
            688,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 57. When the sun is at 159 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            58,
            6,
            30,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 98. When the sun is at 46 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            103,
            101,
            102,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 6000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 913000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            996,
            595,
            764,
            0.007
        ],
        "answer": 0.007
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 mat, 40 couch, 77 cycles, 4 plants, and 14 cat? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            314,
            382,
            32,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            5,
            -26,
            21,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 3 feet?",
        "options": [
            2104,
            9560,
            1728,
            1405
        ],
        "answer": 1728
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 41 ohms and 21 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            21,
            9,
            20,
            861,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 table, 7 refrigerator, 53 bed, 2 human beings, and 15 snail? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            18,
            17,
            18,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cook wants to put a car in a road.The road is 5.874 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 2.0,
        "options": [
            20.0,
            2.0,
            2.1,
            5.874
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 35cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            4,
            28,
            39,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 19 ohms and 36 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            19,
            5,
            36,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 table, 7 refrigerator, 53 bed, 2 human beings, and 15 snail? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            0,
            236,
            306
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 16 lemons , how many lemons can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            16,
            30,
            46,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            11,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Garcia wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 16cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            29,
            44,
            37,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 85 grapes , how many grapes can a man eat?",
        "answer": 80,
        "options": [
            85,
            80,
            165,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 2 feet?",
        "options": [
            7510,
            518,
            1152,
            8978
        ],
        "answer": 1152
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 broom, 20 pair of shoes, 43 sofa, 11 cat, and 13 crows? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            304,
            373,
            0,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Vivaan increased from 825 per month to 885 per month while the salary of Scott increased from 405 to 411 and of Burns increased from 553 to 983 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Burns",
        "options": [
            "Vivaan",
            "Scott",
            "Burns",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            0,
            10,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Morales wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 9.639 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 5.98,
        "options": [
            9.639,
            6.08,
            59.800000000000004,
            5.98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 46 ohms and 11 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 25 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            11,
            53,
            57,
            506,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            1,
            10,
            11,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 27 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            27,
            10,
            37,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 31.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            224,
            456,
            138,
            130.2
        ],
        "answer": 130.2
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 11 chocolates , how many chocolates can a man eat?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            11,
            14,
            25,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 bed, 57 table, 12 fan, 13 fungi spots, and 9 people? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            23,
            30,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 85000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 26000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            3269.231,
            916,
            821,
            501
        ],
        "answer": 3269.231
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Owens increased from 874 per month to 974 per month while the salary of Olson increased from 539 to 691 and of Wright increased from 529 to 581 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Wright",
        "options": [
            "Owens",
            "Olson",
            "Wright",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Powell wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 11cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            2,
            12,
            18,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 40.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            279,
            489,
            242.2,
            355
        ],
        "answer": 242.2
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 71000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 529000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            134215.501,
            14,
            582,
            511
        ],
        "answer": 134215.501
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 chair, 26 pair of shoes, 88 cycles, 15 cockroaches, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            103,
            32,
            120,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 80 miles in 10 hours and 53 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.493249104558655,
            3.3226023560730416,
            7.3506891271056665,
            8.623656470588282
        ],
        "answer": 7.3506891271056665
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 21 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 18 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            48,
            39,
            27,
            567,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reed wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 33cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            34,
            42,
            44,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 93000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 326000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            285276.074,
            366,
            571,
            393
        ],
        "answer": 285276.074
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 42 miles in 9 hours and 43 minutes?",
        "options": [
            3.685842393499625,
            7.861402914463651,
            3.9213113233697383,
            0.07204116638078903
        ],
        "answer": 0.07204116638078903
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 32.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            387,
            224,
            195.2,
            308
        ],
        "answer": 195.2
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            8,
            26,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 25.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            94,
            312,
            64,
            55.6
        ],
        "answer": 55.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $56 to the charity and a total of $7644 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            803,
            756,
            136,
            413
        ],
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 15 apples , how many apples can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            15,
            21,
            36,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 3 feet by 1 feet?",
        "options": [
            8610,
            4662,
            432,
            4278
        ],
        "answer": 432
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 29 lemons , how many lemons can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            29,
            11,
            40,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 13 apples , how many apples can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            13,
            23,
            36,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 49000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 989000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            0.05,
            576,
            571,
            630
        ],
        "answer": 0.05
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 18. When the sun is at 25 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            7,
            69,
            14,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 table, 7 refrigerator, 53 bed, 2 human beings, and 15 snail? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            18,
            55,
            72,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 30 flower vase, 24 sofa, 2 plants, and 2 dog? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            71,
            36,
            71,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 9 table, 29 sofa, 61 tubelight, 4 snail, and 12 dog? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            38,
            17,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 35 ohms and 21 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            735,
            0,
            3,
            56,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Olson wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 4.315 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 3.07,
        "options": [
            30.7,
            3.17,
            3.07,
            4.315
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $42 to the charity and a total of $10136 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            241,
            558,
            782,
            874
        ],
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 35000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 880000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            39.773,
            203,
            440,
            611
        ],
        "answer": 39.773
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 17000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 938000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            18123.667,
            216,
            35,
            839
        ],
        "answer": 18123.667
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Gutierrez increased from 404 per month to 879 per month while the salary of Alvarez increased from 433 to 687 and of Martinez increased from 559 to 660 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Martinez",
        "options": [
            "Gutierrez",
            "Alvarez",
            "Martinez",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            27,
            -27,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 21 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            21,
            23,
            44,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cole wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 8.831 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 4.85,
        "options": [
            4.949999999999999,
            48.5,
            4.85,
            8.831
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Veer wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 5cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            7,
            6,
            3,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 12 bed, 39 cycles, 13 crows, and 6 cat? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            72,
            27,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hunter wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 6.577 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 2.79,
        "options": [
            2.79,
            27.9,
            6.577,
            2.89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 24.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            175,
            496,
            151.2,
            425
        ],
        "answer": 151.2
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 38.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            306.8,
            340,
            440,
            454
        ],
        "answer": 306.8
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            27,
            -27,
            22,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 cycles, 75 bed, 7 sofa, 2 snail, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            79,
            0,
            182,
            217
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Payne wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 9.012 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 4.22,
        "options": [
            9.012,
            42.199999999999996,
            4.22,
            4.319999999999999
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 53 miles in 1 hours and 48 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.7851851851851853,
            9.177741741868887,
            1.224174593790007,
            6.649135934578698
        ],
        "answer": 0.7851851851851853
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 3 men, 2 women, 7 children of less than 10 years, 9 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            104,
            21,
            0,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $98 to the charity and a total of $4522 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            46,
            850,
            444,
            111
        ],
        "answer": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 70 miles in 10 hours and 25 minutes?",
        "options": [
            4.436695486671914,
            10.752,
            6.934581305721554,
            1.9201997329061342
        ],
        "answer": 10.752
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Monday and returns to the bank 7years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Monday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "Monday",
            "tuesday",
            "Wednesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 fan, 33 empty boxes, 30 tubelight, 2 dog, and 12 cat? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            32,
            75,
            74,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 96 miles in 7 hours and 7 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.539179757344595,
            4.449998400302731,
            13.489461358313818,
            3.7600813926766703
        ],
        "answer": 13.489461358313818
    },
    {
        "question": "Turner wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 6cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            2,
            8,
            7,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 18 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            24,
            12,
            -24
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 33 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/6 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            16.5,
            53,
            97,
            38
        ],
        "answer": 16.5
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 21 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            6,
            11,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 48000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 567000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            788,
            178,
            84656.085,
            174
        ],
        "answer": 84656.085
    },
    {
        "question": "Miller wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 5.15 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 2.17,
        "options": [
            21.7,
            5.15,
            2.17,
            2.27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 19 years old in the year 1514.In his greatest win, he looted 11227120 of 9393723710 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1726,
            1695,
            1786,
            1495
        ],
        "answer": 1495
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 50 ohms and 47 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            97,
            8,
            2350,
            0,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 16.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            247,
            50.5,
            252,
            62
        ],
        "answer": 50.5
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 168 grapes , how many grapes can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            168,
            76,
            244,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 30 flower vase, 24 sofa, 2 plants, and 2 dog? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            0,
            225,
            256,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            5,
            -26,
            21,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 5 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            393,
            5040,
            8406,
            5885
        ],
        "answer": 5040
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 5 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            5040,
            7673,
            7852,
            9149
        ],
        "answer": 5040
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 chair, 7 tubelight, 2 bed, 9 algae spots, and 12 dog? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            16,
            8,
            33,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 pair of shoes, 19 bed, 60 tubelight, 5 cockroaches, and 15 cat? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            15,
            108,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 27 lemons , how many lemons can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            27,
            14,
            41,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 6 ohms and 32 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 13 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            13,
            33,
            192,
            32,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Spencer wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 35cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            8,
            25,
            40,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 10 feet by 10 feet?",
        "options": [
            1231,
            14400,
            3732,
            5680
        ],
        "answer": 14400
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 3 sofa, 13 pair of shoes, 5 cat, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            37,
            45,
            24,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 50 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 1/6 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            8.33,
            30,
            74,
            66
        ],
        "answer": 8.33
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 5 ohms and 20 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 24 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            24,
            25,
            49,
            20,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 47 miles in 8 hours and 46 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.011172238415224,
            6.908948220819212,
            5.361216730038023,
            3.8939066807266296
        ],
        "answer": 5.361216730038023
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 97000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 85000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            818,
            1.141,
            694,
            101
        ],
        "answer": 1.141
    },
    {
        "question": "Nichols wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 8.666 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 1.3,
        "options": [
            1.4000000000000001,
            13.0,
            8.666,
            1.3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 1000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 82000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            0.012,
            921,
            121,
            776
        ],
        "answer": 0.012
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 33.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            363,
            451,
            284,
            132.6
        ],
        "answer": 132.6
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Patel wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 19cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            31,
            32,
            43,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 89000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 585000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            862,
            152.137,
            663,
            335
        ],
        "answer": 152.137
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 50 fan, 58 sofa, 4 cat, and 3 dog? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            34,
            121,
            126,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wright wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 21cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            21,
            45,
            10,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 68 miles in 1 hours and 24 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.190375563789521,
            1.9810507122934395,
            7.679791878160547,
            77.71428571428572
        ],
        "answer": 77.71428571428572
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            9,
            12,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 18.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            143.8,
            488,
            451,
            324
        ],
        "answer": 143.8
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 54000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 893000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            60.47,
            843,
            206,
            720
        ],
        "answer": 60.47
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 49 ohms and 47 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            47,
            3,
            49,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 80 grapes , how many grapes can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 125,
        "options": [
            80,
            125,
            205,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 43.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            347.6,
            453,
            476,
            421
        ],
        "answer": 347.6
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 flower vase, 90 pair of shoes, 18 refrigerator, 3 cockroaches, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            133,
            133,
            135,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 84000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 342000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            573,
            79,
            245614.035,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 245614.035
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -19,
            18,
            19,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            16,
            3,
            8,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 12 ohms and 49 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 15 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            588,
            39,
            61,
            15,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 bed, 9 sofa, 93 couch, 11 people, and 7 cockroaches? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            104,
            11,
            18,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1788.In his greatest win, he looted 379838035 of 1813040275 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1776,
            1787,
            1866,
            1884
        ],
        "answer": 1776
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnav wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 3.663 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 1.76,
        "options": [
            1.76,
            1.86,
            17.6,
            3.663
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elliott wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 6cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            28,
            20,
            4,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Mendoza increased from 328 per month to 637 per month while the salary of Castillo increased from 590 to 855 and of Ellis increased from 646 to 792 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Ellis",
        "options": [
            "Mendoza",
            "Castillo",
            "Ellis",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kabir wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 4.788 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 3.62,
        "options": [
            4.788,
            3.62,
            36.2,
            3.72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            9,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Diya increased from 764 per month to 855 per month while the salary of Rogers increased from 428 to 967 and of Ahana increased from 790 to 995 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Ahana",
        "options": [
            "Diya",
            "Rogers",
            "Ahana",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 66 miles in 5 hours and 44 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.6751121876735855,
            18.41860465116279,
            5.950635626104179,
            9.332400654542354
        ],
        "answer": 18.41860465116279
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 18 apples , how many apples can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            18,
            29,
            47,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 19 chocolates , how many chocolates can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            19,
            23,
            42,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 broom, 20 pair of shoes, 43 sofa, 11 cat, and 13 crows? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            28,
            96,
            65,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 82 miles in 2 hours and 32 minutes?",
        "options": [
            51.789473684210535,
            2.7326927817161595,
            2.2084340398993323,
            4.402190608957307
        ],
        "answer": 51.789473684210535
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 100000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 586000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            170.648,
            509,
            507,
            296
        ],
        "answer": 170.648
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            3,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            20,
            -23,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Saturday and returns to the bank 9years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Monday",
        "options": [
            "Friday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Monday",
            "Friday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arjun wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 35cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            16,
            38,
            20,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 66 miles in 9 hours and 3 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.743562366134498,
            9.105373782338681,
            0.194475138121547,
            1.1548537243955752
        ],
        "answer": 0.194475138121547
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            10,
            2,
            3,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 40 ohms and 42 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 14 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            1680,
            38,
            14,
            42,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            25,
            -25,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 empty boxes, 3 sofa, 13 pair of shoes, 5 cat, and 15 algae spots? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            49,
            44,
            20,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 10 cake , how many cake can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            10,
            4,
            14,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Morgan earns $10 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $4 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Morgan was paid $4400, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            249,
            342,
            481,
            413
        ],
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            10,
            -25,
            15,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            25,
            -25,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyra earns $8 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Kyra was paid $3490, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            37,
            195,
            322,
            398
        ],
        "answer": 398
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 21 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            567,
            0,
            48,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 29. When the sun is at 80 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            80,
            102,
            18,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            1,
            9,
            2,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mitchell wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 7cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            5,
            14,
            5,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            1,
            5,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 41 ohms and 30 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            30,
            41,
            71,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Siya wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 23cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            13,
            29,
            21,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 7 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            25,
            5,
            -25,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 62 miles in 9 hours and 44 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.369863013698629,
            9.045413177227301,
            2.773350610689311,
            6.493888952083751
        ],
        "answer": 6.369863013698629
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 44 miles in 2 hours and 54 minutes?",
        "options": [
            15.17241379310345,
            1.7216654291590798,
            7.492461413105233,
            5.348785596406991
        ],
        "answer": 15.17241379310345
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 broom, 33 refrigerator, 41 pair of shoes, 8 cat, and 11 human beings? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            400,
            370,
            0,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gonzalez began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 136,
        "options": [
            136,
            0,
            137,
            138
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 broom, 23 fan, 5 couch, 10 algae spots, and 5 trees? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            34,
            40,
            15,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            -1,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Saanvi began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 231,
        "options": [
            231,
            0,
            233,
            232
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 broom, 23 fan, 5 couch, 10 algae spots, and 5 trees? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            40,
            39,
            34,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jimenez wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 14cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            35,
            20,
            22,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 145,
        "options": [
            147,
            146,
            145,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            13,
            13,
            14,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 21 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            6,
            11,
            -17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Torres wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 7cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            11,
            5,
            12,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            -25,
            25,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 empty boxes, 83 flower vase, 50 broom, 7 trees, and 9 dog? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 122,
        "options": [
            122,
            151,
            163,
            160
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            0,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 36 ohms and 39 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            39,
            75,
            6,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 flower vase, 33 table, 84 cycles, 15 pigeons, and 8 human beings? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            332,
            15,
            0,
            347
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            10,
            -25,
            15,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            20,
            -23,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 6 cake , how many cake can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            6,
            3,
            9,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 13 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            28,
            25,
            3,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Edwards wants to put a car in a road.The road is 5.356 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 3.95,
        "options": [
            39.5,
            3.95,
            5.356,
            4.05
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 sofa, 61 table, 63 bed, 8 snail, and 10 fungi spots? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            71,
            18,
            62,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dixon wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 19cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            14,
            26,
            25,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Washington wants to put a car in a road.The road is 7.74 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 2.75,
        "options": [
            2.85,
            2.75,
            7.74,
            27.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 72. When the sun is at 50 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            101,
            96,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Diaz wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 39cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            38,
            40,
            5,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 70000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 661000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            13,
            368,
            0.106,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 0.106
    },
    {
        "question": "Aditya wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 32cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            23,
            18,
            19,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 53 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 2/7 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            82,
            15.14,
            57,
            37
        ],
        "answer": 15.14
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 13.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            31.4,
            336,
            493,
            85
        ],
        "answer": 31.4
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 7 ohms and 29 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            5,
            36,
            21,
            203,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 empty boxes, 83 flower vase, 50 broom, 7 trees, and 9 dog? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            98,
            17,
            16,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 24 ohms and 25 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            25,
            49,
            24,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 70. When the sun is at 144 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            63,
            16,
            67,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 14 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            7,
            28,
            0,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 empty boxes, 83 flower vase, 50 broom, 7 trees, and 9 dog? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            109,
            65,
            138,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            19,
            7,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "White began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            67,
            66,
            0,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 19 ohms and 32 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            19,
            3,
            32,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            3,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 14 ohms and 22 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            22,
            9,
            36,
            27,
            308
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -28,
            28,
            22,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $66 to the charity and a total of $11392 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            750,
            877,
            594,
            172
        ],
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            -1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 10 men, 4 women, 9 children of less than 10 years, 9 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            114,
            32,
            0,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 bed, 33 cycles, 47 table, 12 snail, and 12 bed bugs? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            31,
            10,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Romero earns $18 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Romero was paid $1759, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            127,
            97,
            468,
            391
        ],
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 76. When the sun is at 65 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            24,
            77,
            106,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 2 cake , how many cake can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            2,
            9,
            11,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 broom, 20 pair of shoes, 43 sofa, 11 cat, and 13 crows? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            33,
            54,
            24,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 18 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            12,
            24,
            12,
            -24
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 chair, 7 tubelight, 2 bed, 9 algae spots, and 12 dog? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            22,
            11,
            12,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 71 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 2/10 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            68,
            30,
            14.2,
            69
        ],
        "answer": 14.2
    },
    {
        "question": "Dixon wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 32cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            16,
            24,
            40,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anaya wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 7cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            8,
            4,
            8,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 tubelight, 25 chair, 99 fan, 3 snail, and 5 trees? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            11,
            86,
            5,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Allen wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 23cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            7,
            13,
            10,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 75 grapes , how many grapes can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 129,
        "options": [
            75,
            129,
            204,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 4 cake , how many cake can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            4,
            5,
            9,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 43 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            70,
            43,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 empty boxes, 60 cycles, 58 refrigerator, 1 pigeons, and 11 trees? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 128,
        "options": [
            129,
            70,
            59,
            128
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anaya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 175,
        "options": [
            176,
            0,
            177,
            175
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 61 miles in 9 hours and 48 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.694691689346786,
            9.959183673469388,
            1.9010298342074259,
            8.5958218047408
        ],
        "answer": 9.959183673469388
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Saturday and returns to the bank 11years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Wednesday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Friday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Monday"
        ]
    }
]